[
  {
    "answer": "sloshy",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "sloshy",
      "Peter Frampton",
      "Limozeen",
      "Taranchula"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is NOT one of Strong Bads favorite bands in the Internet cartoon Homestar Runner?",
    "questionId": "5f03da2f06bfb557edb566be8a58a6ea",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Rampion",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Rampion",
      "Turnip",
      "Lettuce",
      "Safflower"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Speaking of the famous fairy tale, that girl with the long hair was named which of these plants?",
    "questionId": "7adc2dfcb7defd83607a766f5da04854",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Twists the fibres into a thread",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Collects the finished thread",
      "Powers the wheel",
      "Twists the fibres into a thread",
      "Sorts the finished threads"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Sleeping Beauty pricked her finger on the part of a spinning wheel that does this.",
    "questionId": "5326ad9e30dc2514ec3c624b3176bca8",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Glass shoes sound like something a princess would wear.",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Glass shoes sound like something a princess would wear.",
      "Vair (fur), was mistaken for verre (glass).",
      "They were a symbol of her purity.",
      "Glass shoes were worn by royalty."
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Why does Cinderella wear a glass slipper?",
    "questionId": "951ce91315078d0aea5ad6849cc6f02b",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "A daughter of the air.",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "A block-buster animated film.",
      "Foam on the waves.",
      "A mermaid again.",
      "A daughter of the air."
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "The Little Mermaid refused to kill the prince, so she eventually ends up as this.",
    "questionId": "0e346eccb630bb995c35be496bc1707c",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Wooden hair.",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Hemophiliac lips.",
      "Rosaceae cheeks.",
      "Ice crystal eyes.",
      "Wooden hair."
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Only one of the following descriptions of the features of Snow White is true.  Can you spot it?",
    "questionId": "eb11e293eeae768f108ed296c4ba7705",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Dry stalks of wheat.",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Dried stalks of marsh plant.",
      "Dry stalks of grass.",
      "Dry stalks of corn.",
      "Dry stalks of wheat."
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Referring to a well-known fairy tale, the millers daughter had to spin what?",
    "questionId": "305dbfeeddbdbc83934267295d43fd13",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Eastern Europe",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "England",
      "Italy",
      "Eastern Europe",
      "The Middle East"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "The witch in Hansel and Gretel was probably raised in this part of the world.",
    "questionId": "a407f4b65bd7c462b2b2841adfb81592",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Crayon",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Quill pen",
      "Fireplace",
      "Crayon",
      "Horn book"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which of the following items cannot be found in a colonial classroom?",
    "questionId": "6e273bda96d43bd25d87509293e67ea7",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Reading McGuffey",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Skateboarding",
      "Using a dishwasher",
      "Reading McGuffey",
      "Ordering pizza"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Colonial people spend some of their free time doing which of these?",
    "questionId": "d2cca4b596a3b4c489534b8e5ea23f50",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Worked as an apprentice",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Went to school",
      "Worked on his autobiography",
      "Worked on many inventions, including electricity",
      "Worked as an apprentice"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "From age 12 to 21, American activist and politician Benjamin Franklin did what?",
    "questionId": "24709cbf6a4345fbc1204e0892390857",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Jane Addams",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Jane Addams",
      "Harriet Tubman",
      "Betty Ross",
      "Florence Nightingale"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In 1889, this person founded the Hull House, one of the first settlement houses in the U.S.",
    "questionId": "b8fac1bfe987ddcd9f59412454d74820",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "I have not yet begun to fight.",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "I have a dream.",
      "Give me liberty or give me death.",
      "I have not yet begun to fight.",
      "I shall return."
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which of the following is a famous quote by John Paul Jones, the well-known American naval hero from the American Revolutionary War?",
    "questionId": "67a8d927e5e7a7217c6f3d79115997de",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Declaration of Independence",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Emancipation Proclamation",
      "Louisiana Purchase",
      "Declaration of Independence",
      "Boston Tea Party"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which of the following events is associated with Independence Day?",
    "questionId": "6e15e896a02e391d6c681a5c3b6b3600",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "1498",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "1588",
      "1498",
      "1600",
      "1763"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What year did Columbus first arrive on American land?",
    "questionId": "5fc13107d62968184cf6c0e3591c64ef",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Anteater",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Dolphin",
      "Seal",
      "Anteater",
      "Kangaroo"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "You can see this animal around ant-hill. It is almost 6 feet long and it likes to eat ants.",
    "questionId": "85688b1a84675f175d9bb93569ecc23f",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Bear",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Fox",
      "Bear",
      "Cheetah",
      "Horse"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "It is a big animal with brown fur and it likes eating fish and honey. It has 42 teeth.",
    "questionId": "078edac3f06d86e2eb13146258a91134",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Cockroach",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Ant",
      "Fly",
      "Cockroach",
      "Grasshopper"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "This is a repulsive insect either black or brown. It can live a couple of weeks with its head cut off.",
    "questionId": "cbc29cb23d6286c2abfd37677d8e8db2",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Elephant",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Elephant",
      "Rabbit",
      "Bear",
      "Horse"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "This is a big and grey animal with wide ears and a trunk. It cannot hop.",
    "questionId": "29ea29b609354962ce919774f0786bf1",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Chow Chow",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Chow Chow",
      "Pitbull",
      "Hound",
      "Setter"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "This is a fluffy dog. It has a black-black or purple tongue.",
    "questionId": "14ea0d83c2e1c82fb6261f2f4ba56670",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Giraffe",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Giraffe",
      "Elephant",
      "Zebra",
      "Camel"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "This animal lives in Africa. It has a really long neck and eats leaves. It produces almost no sounds.",
    "questionId": "ef932b7bb1c23515c6d43e1aca07e345",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Rat",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Cat",
      "Anteater",
      "Rat",
      "Weasel"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "This animal is similar to a mouse but it is bigger. It can give birth to more than 160 babies in a year.",
    "questionId": "7e1b020e73a404fe1c838d106a8482b3",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Snakes",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Snakes",
      "Frogs",
      "Fish",
      "Eel"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "These animals are long and slim. They creep. Most of them can go an entire year without eating at all!",
    "questionId": "db2407cb8c6340cd2db3cb69eb796841",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Dolphins",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Mackerel",
      "Dolphins",
      "Salmon",
      "Tuna fish"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "These animals live in the sea. They are very friendly to humans. Although they resemble fish, they will drown if kept underwater for too long.",
    "questionId": "36558a3cb9b5fddbc96b9f414466d104",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Skunk",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Skunk",
      "Turbot",
      "Horse",
      "Deer"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "When this animal wants to defend itself, it throws a nasty smell toward its aggressor. This smell can be detected by a human a mile away.",
    "questionId": "225c9cfbb665f8179ef70b07aa59c734",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "The path in which electricity travels is called an electric circuit.",
    "questionId": "d1610a8628a0118d98cf2f9bb573ce41",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Seasons change because the Earth is getting closer and further from the sun.",
    "questionId": "0dcc8f92a6f9af04142dacbb79047f8c",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Stars vanish during the day.",
    "questionId": "44338df5f9a3a93c008b2438572d615d",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "There are 4 basic conditions needed to produce an echo.",
    "questionId": "11344f074fd0c1d521cef89b616b3caa",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Peter, Susan, Edmund, Lucy",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Peter, Annie, Alan, Lucy",
      "Peter, Susan, Edmund, Sydney",
      "Peter, Susan, Edmund, Lucy",
      "Peter, Sally, Edward, Lucinda"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What are the names of the four children in the story The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe?",
    "questionId": "da22692f2d573aa765dcf24d62fefb53",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The White Witch",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "The Red Witch",
      "The Evil Witch",
      "The Terrible Witch of the West",
      "The White Witch"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which character is the enemy of the four children in the movie The Chronicles of Narnia: The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe?",
    "questionId": "8adeca17758587f79a0d063c9b649630",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the movie The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe, Susan is the oldest of the four children.",
    "questionId": "fcaaee5c31083768780dbbb57c01a34c",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Turkish Delight",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Turkish Delight",
      "Laffy Taffy",
      "Jolly Rancher",
      "Turkish Joy"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the movie The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe Edmund asked if the White Witch had what candy?",
    "questionId": "63c69b8cc7982b9ef499764d8addb1b4",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "true",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the movie The Lion, The Witch, and The Wardrobe, Lucy discovered the wardrobe while the children were playing hide and seek.",
    "questionId": "687f2312c21b8c2b265b85060146ef7e",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "blue",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "green",
      "brown",
      "hazel",
      "blue"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What was the colour of Susans eyes in the movie The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe?",
    "questionId": "5793e2187394dea53fc3b372145bd176",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "false",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Peter is the second of the Pevensie children to enter Narnia in the film The Lion, The Witch, and The Wardrobe.",
    "questionId": "52a966ec4ef61d71bf10e07dd1412cf8",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "The action in the movie The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe begins in 1940 during a German bombing raid of London.",
    "questionId": "11e61921867765de3c7102a1ec31ad47",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Tumnus",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Taurus",
      "Tamus",
      "Tumnus",
      "Timus"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the name of the faun that Lucy meets in The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe?",
    "questionId": "155f4752748c052887c112a146ba20aa",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "The lion that the children meet in the end of the movie The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobeis called Aslan.",
    "questionId": "11eda0b87972a8e3ac9016d7c09ebb2d",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Felix Felicis",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Felix Felicis",
      "Polyjuice Potion",
      "none of these",
      "Avada Kedava"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the name of the potion that grants good luck, mentioned in Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince?",
    "questionId": "65af70e7404f6711e38cc88a8033b3d5",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Cho",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Hermione",
      "Cho",
      "Ginny",
      "Blaise"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which of these characters kissed Harry after a lesson of DA in Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix?",
    "questionId": "e313cc55572d338b043061cf74d65212",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The Headless Hunt",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "The Order of the Phoenix",
      "The Headless Hunt",
      "The Triwizard Cup",
      "The DA"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What group did Nearly-headless Nick never become a part of in Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets?",
    "questionId": "bf48f96ec15897239edd58327e2da4bf",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "James Potter, Remus Lupin, Sirius Black",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "James Potter, Remus Lupin, Sirius Black",
      "James Potter, Remus Lupin",
      "James Potter, Sirius Black, Peter Pettigrew",
      "James Potter only"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which of the following characters are described as trustworthy in Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban?",
    "questionId": "96337910584bba06a9e666e4c7a717db",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Albus Percival Wulfric Brian Dumbledore",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Albus Percival Dumbledore",
      "Albus Wulfric Dumbledore",
      "Albus Percival Wulfric Brian Dumbledore",
      "He never revealed his full name in the books"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "According to the Harry Potter books, what is the full name of Dumbledore, the headmaster of Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry?",
    "questionId": "d2effc97da0037f33c2b615c8b8ef7ba",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Dumbledore was in contact with Sirius Black in Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire.",
    "questionId": "75ee3b45158f4efbc256fcdaa7ff90d0",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Add a clockwise stir after every seventh counterclockwise stir",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Stir clockwise until the potion turns as clear as water",
      "Add a counterclockwise stir after every seventh clockwise stir",
      "Stir counterclockwise until the potion turns as clear as water",
      "Add a clockwise stir after every seventh counterclockwise stir"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince, the half-blood prince tells Harry to do what to his potion?",
    "questionId": "8099f8d6494f49b0b11e1554da20880d",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Hippogriff",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Manticore",
      "Unicorn",
      "Hippogriff",
      "Bird"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What kind of creature was Buckbeak from the book Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban?",
    "questionId": "2a7330df48528d83637f047d70060ebf",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Hermione",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Dudley",
      "Ron",
      "Hermione",
      "Ms. Weasley"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Who was the last person to talk to Harry at the end of Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets?",
    "questionId": "6b6c662862a8c35fb9804b58740d1edc",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Fluffy",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Fluffy",
      "Norbert",
      "Aragog",
      "Fang"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the Harry Potter books, what is the name of Hagrids three-headed dog?",
    "questionId": "7a9476892b3ec592d0173525d16b8979",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Sirius Black",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Sirius Black",
      "Remus Lupin",
      "Peter Pettigrew",
      "James Potter"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "According to the Harry Potter books, who is Harrys godfather?",
    "questionId": "9de110a4d0573642c0c41db54bf47a49",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Harry Potter and the Philosophers Stone",
      "Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince",
      "Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix",
      "She doesnt get fired in the books"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In what book of the Harry Potter series does professor Trelawney get fired?",
    "questionId": "71d3963e5108dd7494ac8c77c28ced40",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Hermione Jean Granger",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Hermione Cassandra Granger",
      "It was never mentioned.",
      "Hermione James Dumbledore",
      "Hermione Jean Granger"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the Harry Potter books, what is Harrys classmate Hermiones full name?",
    "questionId": "52aacc4088cac397e519590800fd8218",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Harry Potter and the Sorcerers Stone",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban",
      "Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire",
      "Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets",
      "Harry Potter and the Sorcerers Stone"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In which movie did Hermione Granger say the following: Im going to bed, before either one of you have another clever idea to get us killed, or worse, expelled",
    "questionId": "fd2ef934d76cb2d6176c58192405c9f1",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "that it was jinxed and was given to Harry by Sirius Black",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "that it was jinxed and was given to Harry by Sirius Black",
      "that it was given to Harry by Dumbledore because he felt bad after Harrys broom was demolished by the Whomping Willow",
      "that it was amazing and wanted to be the first to ride it after Harry",
      "that it was jinxed and was given to Harry by Lucius Malfoy who was still angry about the loss of his House Elf"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What did Hermione Granger, a character from the Harry Potter series, think about the Firebolt?",
    "questionId": "a8d53264fa29dca32182528fce828fdd",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "It is stated in the Harry Potter books that Hermione Grangers parents are teachers.",
    "questionId": "ca805d9ea6207ee23b8c1c64a13da248",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "false",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Hermione was able to see the Thresals in Harry Potter and The Order of the Phoenix.",
    "questionId": "b14f623e1e982d9f86287cc82ba419d0",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the Harry Potter series, Hermiones full name is Hermione Denise Granger.",
    "questionId": "fd19d7a757566a0b046e8a01a124bacc",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Baseball Bat",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Baseball Wand",
      "Baseball Bat",
      "Baseball Raquet",
      "Baseball Club"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the wooden stick used to hit a baseball called?",
    "questionId": "d8c6694ceb46245c9952a6d82305abe2",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "White",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Green",
      "White",
      "Black",
      "Blue"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What color is a major league baseball?",
    "questionId": "7f5777e298e423924a3d86ce688bec48",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "true",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "You should wear a helmet while hitting a baseball.",
    "questionId": "503667f15b6db7dd250f31b1a30a4028",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Home Run",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Home Run",
      "Stolen Base",
      "Hat Trick",
      "3 Pointer"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is it called when you hit a baseball out of the park?",
    "questionId": "7067a74551d853983b39712e2e4bd71b",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Baseball Glove",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Baseball Helmet",
      "Baseball Glove",
      "Baseball Mittens",
      "Baseball Shoes"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What do you wear on your hand when playing the field in baseball?",
    "questionId": "b05cd268d2983d42b7086667be9865e3",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Catcher",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Catcher",
      "Short Stop",
      "Manager",
      "Pitcher"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In baseball, what is the name of the player who squats behind the hitter and catches the ball?",
    "questionId": "c916bec8c6273e45b9c1e23f02daa12f",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "When you run the bases in baseball you should run from 3rd base to 1st base.",
    "questionId": "54ae9ce9023317702f00973ecf91a76a",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Pitcher",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Coach",
      "Catcher",
      "Short Stop",
      "Pitcher"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the player who throws the ball to the hitter called in baseball?",
    "questionId": "c27517afdf1d5934feeacd45ef4f3b68",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Baseball is usually played indoors.",
    "questionId": "46d79486f7b3b72fd1b6b5e53f1cda8f",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "$39",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "$44",
      "$35",
      "$39",
      "$37"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Casey has 2 ten dollar bills, 3 five dollar bills, and 4 one dollar bills. How much money does Casey have altogether?",
    "questionId": "a65ed61e44b78eca91062e3257831ad2",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "XXXXXXXX",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "XXXXXXXX",
      "XXXXXXX",
      "XXXXXXXXX",
      "XXXXXXXXXX"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What would be next in this pattern:  XX, XXXX, XXXXXX, ________?",
    "questionId": "5cf93fbaa49ffce4108259e607e0409e",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Pepsi and Nerds",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Reeses Pieces, Nerds, and Gum",
      "Pepsi and Gum",
      "Pepsi and Nerds",
      "Reeses Pieces and Gum"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Reeses Pieces cost $0.60. Nerds cost $0.35. Pepsi costs $0.90. Gum costs $0.45. I have $1.25, and want to spend all of my money. What should I buy?",
    "questionId": "13e8f0ca46eceda49299759642b6f5cb",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "36",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "26",
      "35",
      "36",
      "82"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Chad and Jason have a collection of comic books. Chad has 23 books. Together, Chad and Jason have a total of 59 books. How many books does Jason have?",
    "questionId": "23c0d8a7e98a48a5de00108387165e31",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "35",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "30",
      "35",
      "45",
      "40"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Leah is making chocolate chip cookies. She has 6 groups of 5 chocolate chips each. If she adds one more group of 5 chocolate chips, how many chocolate chips will she have?",
    "questionId": "327480ebe27655e3e20da1e368658226",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "$0.70",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "$0.60",
      "$0.65",
      "$0.70",
      "$0.75"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Stephanie has $0.85. She gives a quarter to Jennifer. In return, Jennifer gives Stephanie a dime. How much money does Stephanie have now?",
    "questionId": "24088d524f77b5b5f1e05c265bc027cb",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "7:35 a.m.",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "7:35 a.m.",
      "7:45 a.m.",
      "8:25 a.m",
      "7:25 a.m."
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Mike has to be to school at 8:00 a.m. If it takes him 25 minutes to walk to school, what time should he leave?",
    "questionId": "e2bad48a59664b2f2d17032a8f0dacf1",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The Boy and His Horse",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Prince Caspian",
      "The Boy and His Horse",
      "The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe",
      "The Voyage of the Dawn Treader"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "The Chronicles of Narnia, written by C.S. Lewis, is a series of seven fantasy novels. Which of the following is not one of the books in this series?",
    "questionId": "c84044990f008a9ee0c00846be9fcc7a",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Eustace",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Caspian",
      "Telmar",
      "Eustace",
      "Digory"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In The Voyage of the Dawn Treader, published in 1952, Edmund and Lucy Pevensie return to Narnia along with their younger cousin named what?",
    "questionId": "86d78ebc0ff8f036938f70117f8555e7",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The Silver Chair",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "The Last Battle",
      "Prince Caspian",
      "The Voyage of the Dawn Treader",
      "The Silver Chair"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "There comes a point when Peter, Susan, Edmund, and Lucy Pevensie are no longer allowed to visit Narnia because they are too old. So the lion calls their young cousin back to Narnia together with Jill, a fellow student of his. This happens in which book of The Chronicles of Narnia series?",
    "questionId": "2c347d09c4d42e5989acae77fc254087",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Edmund",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Lucy",
      "Susan",
      "Edmund",
      "Peter"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which of the Pevensie children is lured into teaming up with the White Witch in the novel The Lion, the Witch and the Wardrobe?",
    "questionId": "137989ef65d4ba44b83a170aadd06c9a",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Ape",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Ape",
      "Centaur",
      "Unicorn",
      "Faun"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In The Last Battle chronicles, which earned C.S. Lewis a Carnegie Medal, two children return to save Narnia from Shift who tricks the donkey Puzzle into impersonating the Great Lion. What kind of creature is Shift?",
    "questionId": "08098a72587cb3dcc4d8b95e6324d64f",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "water ski",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "water ski",
      "bungy jump",
      "walk a tightrope",
      "snow ski"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What can Bungy the budgie do?",
    "questionId": "7e2c18adcf7ea2bfcc39216bed289566",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Arthur Weasley",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Hermione",
      "Sirius Black",
      "Arthur Weasley",
      "Molly Weasley"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Who sent Harry a letter in Chapter 2 telling him not to do any more magic, or to surrender his wand?",
    "questionId": "5c60d21833249b4c43c5e5c44e6d55a0",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Albus Dumbledore",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Sirius Black",
      "Lucius Malfoy",
      "Arthur Weasly",
      "Albus Dumbledore"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Cornelius Fudge thinks that who wants to be the Minister of Magic?",
    "questionId": "f80101a59546b3abf2cf58533580716d",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Regulus",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Regulus",
      "Tom",
      "Ronald",
      "Remus"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "This person is Siriuss brother.",
    "questionId": "c0034440aeb4899ec60f76bd1a2567d4",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Luna Lovegood was reading the Quippler on the Hogwarts Express.",
    "questionId": "f481046ce05bd9ecd5db2206b43bf20f",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Llewellyn",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Llewellyn",
      "Corwin",
      "Blaise",
      "Diedre"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What ward was Arthur Weasly in while at St Mungos?",
    "questionId": "46fff1ee7b890bc9f4a7d2066055be40",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Jane",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Jane",
      "Marie",
      "Barbara",
      "Mary"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "This is Professor Umbridges middle name.",
    "questionId": "4974fbdfe3e35dc3fe91b519a26bdacc",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Gurg",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Urg",
      "Gurg",
      "Gurrl",
      "Ugh"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "A giant chief is called this.",
    "questionId": "18bf4070d7e9ff56305cad1625c9d367",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "his Grandfather",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "his Grandmother",
      "no one",
      "his Grandfather",
      "his parents"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Who had Neville Longbottom seen die?",
    "questionId": "f33089b48a7df494cd6d12f8ff3b011b",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Cho",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Cho",
      "Neville",
      "Luna",
      "Ron"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Who did not go with Harry to the Ministry of Magic to rescue Black?",
    "questionId": "78c8daccc0a874734b1cd131f72c8cbd",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Mr. Meaty",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Mr. Fast Food",
      "Mr. Meaty",
      "Mr. Meat",
      "Dr. Burger"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Josh and Parker star on this Nickelodeon show which takes place mostly at a fast food restaurant. What is the name of the show?",
    "questionId": "6b5b64443a6f333c03d8734e24e8d31b",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Jimmy Neutron",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Jimmy Neutron",
      "Drake and Josh",
      "Neutron, Boy Genius",
      "The fairly odd parents"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which of these Nickelodeon animated shows stars a big headed kid who also has a very big brain?",
    "questionId": "296d96095245225add99953f1b89deea",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Water",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Water",
      "Fire",
      "Air",
      "Light"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the show Jimmy Neutron, Jimmy goes to Mars in search of a major power source and runs into some huge rock creatures living on Mars. What substance are these creatures vulnerable to?",
    "questionId": "6c7cb96eeadf679638dc0a83a2077529",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Actor Drake Bell from the Nickelodeon show Drake and Josh founded a band named Drake 24/7 in real life.",
    "questionId": "98ad04e26953569baf7a5ce9c86be1e2",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Nobody dares her that",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Ned Bigby",
      "Simon Nelson Cook",
      "Nobody dares her that",
      "Billy Loomer"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In Neds Declassified School Survival Guide, who dares Moze to wear a frilly dress with flowers for 48 hours?",
    "questionId": "af0779868d35c5b9057249875171859c",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Actress Miranda Cosgrove plays Megan in the hit Nickelodeon show Drake and Josh.",
    "questionId": "4354dd73d84fb0c973f35a11d56fe0eb",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Sam",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "A Lamb",
      "Jean-Claude Van Damme",
      "Sam",
      "Bam-Bam"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Complete this line from the classic childrens book Green Eggs and Ham: I am ______.",
    "questionId": "c30bed4d100b9f5a335f61e7f37825ef",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "The book Green Eggs and Ham was first published in 1952.",
    "questionId": "da636fc07ef0d95761278a61bc18bb3e",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Fourth",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Fourth",
      "Second",
      "First",
      "Third"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Where did Green Eggs and Ham rank according to Publishers Weekly 2001 list of best selling childrens books of all-time?",
    "questionId": "cfe2986b29259b53e04f34fda48149ca",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Rev. Jesse Jackson once read Green Eggs and Ham aloud on the late Night show Saturday Night Live.",
    "questionId": "6654ad36786a930c7da0aa7c0a739726",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Fox",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Dog with Chicken Pox",
      "Bag of Rocks",
      "Clock",
      "Fox"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Complete this line from the book Green Eggs and Ham: I do not like them in a box! I do not like them with a _____!",
    "questionId": "a988cc520a0f90933fe5cdb99bd9d608",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "The book Green Eggs and Ham contains only 50 different words.",
    "questionId": "18ba853507a445f5d81a33668b57e797",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Car",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Line at the DMV",
      "Jeep",
      "Bucket of boiled beets",
      "Car"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What word is missing in this line from the book Green Eggs and Ham: Would you? Could you? In a ........?",
    "questionId": "cc7687ec02836112ff928e427ae74a4d",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Helmet",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Hat",
      "Helmet",
      "Wig",
      "Shoe"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What should you wear on your head when you play American football?",
    "questionId": "da6c94a204b330e5c8db61a748bbde52",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Quarterback",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Quarterback",
      "Running back",
      "Kicker",
      "Tight End"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In American football, the player who throws the ball to the other players on the field is called what?",
    "questionId": "982ded5e1f0d32db7e39da1b6e78e798",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Stick",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Helmet",
      "Stick",
      "Padding",
      "Football"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which of these items is not used in an American football game?",
    "questionId": "ef3ff70b96e8ff0bf6bb1ae8796f158e",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Touchdown",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Touchdown",
      "Three Pointer",
      "Home Run",
      "Hat Trick"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the main method of scoring in American football?",
    "questionId": "8abab2f58c7d70c8279738cac3ff4516",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Dolphins",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Patriots",
      "Dolphins",
      "Yankees",
      "Jets"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the professional team of Miami in American football called?",
    "questionId": "3e59598f355410e042c8a570176a3733",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Field",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Court",
      "Rink",
      "Diamond",
      "Field"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What do you call the grassy area on which an American football game is played?",
    "questionId": "57420bd0c1e5d09550f3477befeeb94d",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Brown and white",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Brown and white",
      "Green and yellow",
      "Pink and purple",
      "Blue and red"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the color of a traditional American football?",
    "questionId": "f09358dac05640af6233df961ba25617",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "6",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "2",
      "4",
      "5",
      "6"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "How many points is a touchdown worth in American football?",
    "questionId": "4e964eee578f78787b7108826f1b4f2b",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Oval",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Rectangle",
      "Square",
      "Oval",
      "Round"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the shape of a traditional American football?",
    "questionId": "f7be7ad02d6fa5b0cf4b017fdcc2ba95",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Coach",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Wide Receiver",
      "Quarterback",
      "Tight End",
      "Coach"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What do you call the man or woman who runs a football team and tells the players what to do?",
    "questionId": "dbd6ffcaadcc5e2f97b2a965bfa1eab6",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "1989",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "1889",
      "1985",
      "1989",
      "1885"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In what year did Disney release the film The Little Mermaid?",
    "questionId": "a6875248bccf287f61e758b872c15342",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Carlotta",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Marianne",
      "Vanessa",
      "Janice",
      "Carlotta"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What was the name of the housemaid that served dinner on Ariels first night in the palace in the movie The Little Mermaid?",
    "questionId": "ab7b2dc7966514e764f04bd05310be9e",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Ursula, one of the characters in the Disney movie The Little Mermaid, is a cecaelia sea witch.",
    "questionId": "41db7fe40013a1247d16144616f0ed70",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Vanessa",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Matilda",
      "Vanessa",
      "Gertrude",
      "Louise"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What name did Ursula adopt while in disguise in the movie The Little Mermaid?",
    "questionId": "2d448444f68c2d2a0e94b409930e56fa",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Buddy Hackett provided the voice of Flounder in the movie The Little Mermaid.",
    "questionId": "a4fc8639f8987b905089c4dc3aeb264e",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "The film The Little Mermaid grossed approximately $200,000,000.",
    "questionId": "293cd29d350237ac9c2e3e98de90fa21",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "The first line in the movie The Little Mermaid was Flounder, quit being such a guppy!.",
    "questionId": "0c41ff949d4968a7a862dc81ceeb4891",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Nov. 29 1990",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Nov. 18 1989",
      "Nov. 29 1990",
      "Nov. 15 1989",
      "Nov. 15 1990"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "When was the film The Little Mermaid released in Germany?",
    "questionId": "7648595bf92c4b06a4aa74024289496a",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "true",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "10 times 10 equals 100.",
    "questionId": "de16016fa5996d0edc2ebf751a363bd4",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "2",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "2",
      "11",
      "4",
      "3"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "How much is 1 + 1?",
    "questionId": "3ba904ffebb0c8ae69e215a8df8f5b69",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "0",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "9",
      "0",
      "10",
      "7"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "If I have ten apples and I give them all to another person, how many do I have left?",
    "questionId": "2a57760d9844f0bca9110624ebb831f4",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "They would be equal",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "The steel",
      "The feathers",
      "None of these",
      "They would be equal"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "If you put 1 gram of steel on one scale and 1 gram of feathers on another one, which one would weigh more?",
    "questionId": "eb89950cda665265782a47cab997516a",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "$300",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "$200",
      "$350",
      "$300",
      "$400"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "If Joe had $900 dollars in life savings and he bought a refrigerator for $600 dollars, how much money would he have left?",
    "questionId": "b343dde3ab41eae4d9dd7d9143eab7f6",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "3.2 are the first numbers in the important mathematical constant pi.",
    "questionId": "80247ff946a7f5036f7d47d121cc6d45",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "false",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In mathematics, a right angle is equal to 100 degrees.",
    "questionId": "05f06de8bbcd6c43d5d0a123b268089e",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "0",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "124,416",
      "9999999",
      "0",
      "124,934"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the final result of the following equation: 3 X 6 X 9 X 0 X 12 X 32 X 2 = ?",
    "questionId": "d2537589e7434e3c4a7a457aa991e275",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "100 multiplied by 0.3 gives 3.00.",
    "questionId": "6ea98c741325e84cfab12e803ce0a9cd",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Roderick",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Brian",
      "Percival",
      "Roderick",
      "Wulfric"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which of these is NOT part of the full name of the fictional character Albus Dumbledore?",
    "questionId": "c8102380320ac17d990a18fb315a6f87",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Transfiguration",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Defense Against the Dark Arts",
      "Transfiguration",
      "Care of Magical Creatures",
      "Potions"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "After graduating from the fictional Hogwarts school, Albus Dumbledore went on to teach this class before becoming headmaster.",
    "questionId": "557b1caaf2f7a26c89c6eb175d7bf086",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "According to the Harry Potter books Albus Dumbledore liked Dementors.",
    "questionId": "8d2c8bc09e9d690742ab61a7b52c2791",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Ring",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Ring",
      "Diary",
      "Necklace",
      "Sword"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince we find out that Albus Dumbledore destroyed one of Voldemorts horcruxes. In what item was the horcrux contained?",
    "questionId": "30284898b641336bb34910093c3b3c58",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Phoenix",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Owl",
      "Phoenix",
      "Demon",
      "Mouse"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the Harry Potter series, one of Albus Dumbledores closest friends and companions is Fawkes, a creature that resides in Dumbledores office. What kind of creature is Fawkes?",
    "questionId": "15cf2c5848326d314e83c8948b271824",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Professor Albus Dumbledores office at the fictional Hogwarts school is protected by a statue of a gargoyle.",
    "questionId": "4bb430ec92db05f7efa93afd4ef47b70",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Raspberry",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Raspberry",
      "Blueberry",
      "Blackberry",
      "Strawberry"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is Albus Dumbledores favorite flavor of jam as revealed in Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince?",
    "questionId": "f5c20ca95dcf6e2d5d9ac46c6e12052a",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "hot",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "humid",
      "hot",
      "dry",
      "wet"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the opposite of cold?",
    "questionId": "47708a4d1e53bf503109c490eedf16da",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "The opposite of open is closed.",
    "questionId": "2ccda9f92c8a8671032bc6c0419bc867",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "right",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "blue",
      "right",
      "maybe",
      "farm"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the opposite of wrong?",
    "questionId": "07713745e31038f32d3e4906eb8fcbf3",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "sad",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "missing",
      "sad",
      "purple",
      "mad"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the opposite of happy?",
    "questionId": "08813e3a92fdb8fa49c1ab8d37f7d4c0",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "huge",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "small",
      "little",
      "huge",
      "miniscule"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which of the following words is NOT an opposite of big?",
    "questionId": "ada2c3c9e700c54f5163c423212ffaa8",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "A word with a meaning opposite to that of another word is called a synonym.",
    "questionId": "95ce1c6accc2ed2e0864ef9822271ebd",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "The opposite of major is minor.",
    "questionId": "c47c9d6cf441452dca43c5a589869029",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "below",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "top",
      "beside",
      "below",
      "green"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the opposite of above?",
    "questionId": "4c90603621a71c303cc7eb35823188d1",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Lilly, James",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Abbie, Harry",
      "Liiy, Harry",
      "Lilly, James",
      "Abbie, James"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What were the first names of Harry Potters parents?",
    "questionId": "691113c405db6a497b23dacfcbd25505",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Ron",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Dudley",
      "Ron",
      "George",
      "Fred"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which of these characters is Harry Potters best friend?",
    "questionId": "0643163ff3dbf2b35b45864057ed694c",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Malfoy, Snape",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Sirius, Remus",
      "Malfoy, Neville",
      "Dumbledore, Snape",
      "Malfoy, Snape"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which of the following are Harry Potters enemies at school?",
    "questionId": "3eeb5f323fd6e679be3def58240e53b6",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Although Harry Potter has a crush on Cho Chang, he ends up with Ginny.",
    "questionId": "763c56e48a44a8da7cfd1e258845e0cf",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "true",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Daniel Radcliffe portrays Harry Potter.",
    "questionId": "31465ab6cb12158c9ab2b4bf6da9f2c6",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Horace Slughorn",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Albus Dumbledoor",
      "Fred Weasley",
      "Serverus Snape",
      "Horace Slughorn"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Who was the potions teacher during Harry Potters sixth year at Hogwarts?",
    "questionId": "0387838484f4b66b10f9c3b3373e6057",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Fictional character Ron Weasley has male siblings only.",
    "questionId": "20065328ab5a0995a44f3ce7abbde84f",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the Harry Potter books, Professor Binns is a ghost that teaches History of Magic.",
    "questionId": "d419658eedec890faecebd071bf397c3",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Rita Skeeter",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Madame Maxime",
      "Mr. Crouch",
      "Ludo Bagman",
      "Rita Skeeter"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Who accused Hermione of having a thing for famous wizards in Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire?",
    "questionId": "18101d19ce5b9894067b1378a12c617d",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Tom Marvolo Riddle",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Tom Voldemort Riddle",
      "Tom Marvolo Riddle",
      "Tom Marvolo Gaunt",
      "Voldemort Tom Riddle"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is Lord Voldemorts real name?",
    "questionId": "eea6f2650b41dfe431a0d008ba3e3e95",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "North America",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Europe",
      "South America",
      "North America",
      "Africa"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "This continent is where Canada, The United States of America, and Mexico are located.",
    "questionId": "04418d07274228c72a58a733b1359248",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Atlantic",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Indian",
      "Atlantic",
      "Arctic",
      "Pacific"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "This ocean is bordered by North and South America on the west and Europe and Africa on the east.",
    "questionId": "1ae16b68c9366f86d460e17efdd86e66",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "A giant spider",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "A griffon",
      "A giant spider",
      "A basilisk",
      "Crumple Horned Snorkak"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the Harry Potter series, Hagrid got kicked out of Hogwarts for possessing what giant creature?",
    "questionId": "8dfe3fcac5b2ed35fffd456fb74f897b",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "A pink umbrella",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "A pink umbrella",
      "A cane",
      "A tree branch",
      "A walking stick"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the Harry Potter books, Hagrid was forbidden to use an actual wand. What did he use instead?",
    "questionId": "80e591bb28bdf65e1d1ea4d9afc24e69",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "A dragon",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "A three-headed dog",
      "A giant Spider",
      "A hippogriff",
      "A dragon"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Hagrid from the Harry Potter series once cared for a creature named Norbert. What was Norbert?",
    "questionId": "5dfde3e4a2ab22067ba8dbe867e7aea7",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "A motorcycle",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "A Carpet",
      "A motorcycle",
      "A ship",
      "A broom"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the Harry Potter series Hagrid gets this flying object from Sirius Black and uses it as his main form of transport.",
    "questionId": "10335f2b7ae9f51d4d97e746c3ba2855",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Hagrid dies in the last installment of the Harry Potter series entitled Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows.",
    "questionId": "c5baab6d84fcb84aa854274d5b0102e7",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Dudley",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Malfoy",
      "Hagrid",
      "Dudley",
      "Ronald"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the name of Harry Potters cousin who often teases and bullies him?",
    "questionId": "9d52fee3e1845128c7e05e5a2523b8ad",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Lily",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Pearl",
      "Hermione",
      "Lily",
      "Angel"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the first name of Harry Potters mother?",
    "questionId": "e8288eff45cb6cc1a5d159dfc78a9e4f",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Professor McGonagall teaches Transfiguration at the fictional Hogwarts school.",
    "questionId": "ae58b63a88bf46581a0f9e7f95fb837b",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "The name of Harry Potters owl is Fawkes.",
    "questionId": "e1911837720544aa2877f394ed0de11a",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Ginny",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Hermione",
      "Ginny",
      "Penelope",
      "Petunia"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the name of Ronald Weasleys younger sister in the Harry Potter books?",
    "questionId": "4236b0c0fdd8efce0518d313b2c3c516",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Professor Snape",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Professor Sprout",
      "Professor Snape",
      "Professor Dumbledore",
      "Professor McGonagall"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "This professor dislikes Harry Potter and unfairly punishes him while favouring Slytherin students.",
    "questionId": "7f578c9b0a97905f13fb2c97bfcb3018",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Gryffindor",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Slytherin",
      "Gryffindor",
      "Ravenclaw",
      "Hufflepuffs"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the name of the Hogwarts house where Harry Potter stayed?",
    "questionId": "6049823768e3d126d19d69e3b5731929",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Fred and George",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Mary and Maria",
      "Al and Ron",
      "Fred and George",
      "Arthur and Artlene"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What are the names of the famous Weasley twins in the Harry Potter series?",
    "questionId": "0d13a34be1f383fe1327704c53cf3c2a",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Harry Potter was the seeker of Gryffindors Quidditch Team.",
    "questionId": "e1d65b6fa6ee206368b9a0e4813b9a9a",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Buckbeak",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Norbert",
      "Buckbeak",
      "Twinky",
      "Aragon"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the name of the hippogriff that hurt Draco Malfoy in the book Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban?",
    "questionId": "7badc433dd1f2c9f059c426b17a1e20b",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "J. K. Rowling",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Judy Blum",
      "J. K. Rowling",
      "E. B. White",
      "J. R. Rowling"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Who wrote the book Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban?",
    "questionId": "f77632ab54e3c8d524156fe4d26b31ab",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "A dog",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "A dog",
      "A snake",
      "A bird",
      "A cat"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the form into which Harry Potters godfather transforms in the book Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban?",
    "questionId": "da07e321c0affe91d669cbb18176f190",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Professor Lupin",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Professor Lupin",
      "Professor Moody",
      "Professor Binns",
      "Professor Dumbledore"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the name of the new Defence Against the Dark Arts teacher who first appears in the novel Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban?",
    "questionId": "5707c31d2bed16137234a13f5ee39b94",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The Patronus Charm",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "A way to become invisible",
      "How to get rid of a boggart",
      "How to sleep without any dreams",
      "The Patronus Charm"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What did the Defence Against the Dark Arts professor teach Harry after the quidditch match in the book Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban?",
    "questionId": "5e9c5bfad936f26877a1682d390a78db",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "He uses the marauders map and his invisibility cloak.",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "He uses the marauders invisible cloak.",
      "None of these",
      "He uses only the marauders map.",
      "He uses the marauders map and his invisibility cloak."
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "How does Harry Potter go to Hogsmede in the third book of the series?",
    "questionId": "8f0e53a2f3bd48b30ea07c26a9b68315",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Werewolves",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Werewolves",
      "Hippogriffs",
      "Mermaids",
      "Boggarts"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban, when Snape taught the Defence Against the Dark Arts, what was the subject the class talked and read about?",
    "questionId": "e2625fce55c05df638ff2c53b3104dc7",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Time Turner",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Time Turner",
      "Hourglass",
      "Changer of Time",
      "Time Stopper"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the device that Hermione uses to travel back in time in Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban?",
    "questionId": "aeb9ac9c038a49e8ff6f697d9e4857e1",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "true",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Harry and Hermione go somewhere, without Ron, at the end of the Harry Potter and The Prisoner of Azkaban.",
    "questionId": "c6c43c3001ff4c8f411df50e675d5716",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "the Queen",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "the Queen",
      "the King",
      "the Princes sister",
      "the Prince"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In Andersens fairy tale The Princess and the Pea, a young woman arrives at the royal familys gate and claims to be a real princess. Who decides to test the validity of her claim by placing a pea under her mattresses?",
    "questionId": "db0c884ebc36a40662bc8357fa96add9",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "their father",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "their father",
      "the with",
      "their stepfather",
      "their mother"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Who takes Hansel and Gretel to the forest and abandons them there in Grimms classic fairy tale?",
    "questionId": "e225bb01194747105bb73c1485182762",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The Snow Queen",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "The Snow Queen",
      "All of these",
      "The Little Match Girl",
      "The Little Mermaid"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which of these fairy tales by Danish author Hans Christian Andersen has a happy ending?",
    "questionId": "cd49d5917f1d8376c39513c91767e0f4",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Bluebeard",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Beauty and the Beast",
      "King Thrushbeard",
      "Rumpelstiltskin",
      "Bluebeard"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In what fairy tale does a curious wife find the dead bodies of her husbands previous wives?",
    "questionId": "ececc716434ad6abe1e45a5ced6677e2",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "a pig",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "a pig",
      "a rooster",
      "a cat",
      "a donkey"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the fairy tale The Musicians of Bremen, four animals decide to become musicians upon finding that they are no longer useful to their owners. Which of the following is not one of the four animals?",
    "questionId": "ab29c6e1654bc78c6c8ba97b5aba25ce",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The Little Mermaid - a key with drops of blood on it",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Aladdin - a lamp",
      "The Little Mermaid - a key with drops of blood on it",
      "Snow White  - a mirror",
      "The Wild Swans - nettle shirts"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which magic object is not correctly matched with the fairy tale?",
    "questionId": "5cead0a487b498e414aa1264f25995d7",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The Emperors New Clothes",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Rapunzel",
      "Sleeping Beauty",
      "The Emperors New Clothes",
      "The Wolf and the Seven Young Kids"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What popular fairy tale is not a recorded folktale, but an original work?",
    "questionId": "8601c0d95b3d608824249c2849f65bdc",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "because her father picked up a flower from the Beasts garden",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "because she picked up a flower from the Beasts garden",
      "because her sisters have stolen an enchanted mirror and a ring from the Beast",
      "because her father picked up a flower from the Beasts garden",
      "because her sisters have stolen jewelry from the Beast"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Why does Belle have to live in the castle with the Beast in the fairy tale The Beauty and the Beast?",
    "questionId": "303aa62feb17325e22924d6bf6768ec1",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Aurora and Philip",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "The Princess is named Aurora, the Prince is anonymous.",
      "Briar-Rose and Stefan",
      "Aurora and Philip",
      "They are anonymous."
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What are the names of the Princess and the Prince in the 1959 Disney animated feature, based on Charles Perrault classic tale Sleeping Beauty?",
    "questionId": "ab4eefa7a4ebadc60724574116ac5fa7",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Thumbelina",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Tom Thumb",
      "The Steadfast Tin Soldier",
      "Hop o My Thumb",
      "Thumbelina"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What diminutive fairy tale character encounters a toad, a beetle, a mouse, a mole and a swallow?",
    "questionId": "9e6c6c71424e3910259cf8d0d0856398",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "17",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "20",
      "17",
      "19",
      "16"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Joe has 20 apples. He gave 2 away to a friend and then he ate one. How many apples did he have after that?",
    "questionId": "bea23afcef9f6421d50a313e71ef1595",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "2",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "8",
      "2",
      "6",
      "4"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What does x equal in this equation?  4x+4=12",
    "questionId": "4e481fc46011c0485ef48de2acf75125",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "37 can be divided into 2 evenly.",
    "questionId": "38e2b7598e7dea8f4ce0180129f75023",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "5",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "5",
      "0",
      "10",
      "2"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the answer to the following: (2*5)-5",
    "questionId": "43b0301ee42224c430bc838a5a6ef6e5",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "The reciprocal of 3/4 is 1 1/3.",
    "questionId": "4eab99d08c2ac0e17b6d6c38730ab775",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "11",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "10",
      "11",
      "12",
      "13"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the square root of 121?",
    "questionId": "8c9bb0b1805fe2eb647fff83592a1df3",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "true",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Is this correct?  2-3+1-4+4-=0",
    "questionId": "f0fa7eedede8d0f50093e9446fe03d33",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "27",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "37",
      "27",
      "207",
      "17"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "One angle in a triangle is 47 degrees and the second angle is 106 degrees. How many degrees are in the third angle?",
    "questionId": "e3c95ff2f8592b05fbad2b7374554b2f",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "16",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "16",
      "17",
      "15",
      "14"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the missing number?  2,4,7,11,?,22",
    "questionId": "a4db0297cc8f66532661bcba1e70f726",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "5",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "4",
      "5",
      "7",
      "6"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "You have a right-angled triangle. You know that one leg is 3 cm long and the second leg is 4 cm long. What is the length of the hypotenuse of that triangle?",
    "questionId": "c7203e0d92359a9ffbc5f4299435305c",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Jamestown in present day Virginia",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Jamestown in present day Virginia",
      "Boston in present day Massachusetts",
      "Providence in what is present day Rhode Island",
      "Charlestown in present day South Carolina"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Founded in 1607, this was the first successful English settlement in what is now the United States.",
    "questionId": "c1f0ccfbb6d76518211697203cb1c4a9",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "France",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Holland",
      "France",
      "Germany",
      "Spain"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Up until 1763, the English and this other European nation fought a series of wars and smaller conflicts to see who would dominate what is now the US and Canada.",
    "questionId": "68ad12506e1137b625757ff88baca074",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "whether the English Parliament or colonial assemblies would control taxes in the colonies",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "whether the English Parliament or colonial assemblies would control taxes in the colonies",
      "religious differences between American colonists and Britain",
      "restrictions on the number of English persons who could move to the English colonies",
      "disagreements between Parliament and the colonies over relations with the Native Americans (Indians)"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What was the biggest issue that eventually led to the English colonies rebellion against their mother country and sparked the American Revolutionary War?",
    "questionId": "e8e7d35ccb7e89a1877877e8385f8786",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "all of these",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "all of these",
      "He was the first president of the United States.",
      "He was a successful Virginia plantation owner.",
      "He was commander of the American Continental Army during the Revolutionary War."
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which of these statements about George Washington is true?",
    "questionId": "5460063441a087cdb58a9da7948b4eae",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Yorktown",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Yorktown",
      "Lexington",
      "Boston",
      "Saratoga"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "The final victory in the American Revolutionary War which convinced the British to grant independence to their former colonies was a victory won by combined French and American forces at this place.",
    "questionId": "b846a094b54f81a505d69a31e4165377",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Andrew Jackson",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "James Polk",
      "Andrew Jackson",
      "Thomas Jefferson",
      "John Adams"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "The seventh president of the United States was the first US president elected from a state west of the Appalachian Mountains (Tennessee). He was also the leader of the US forces who gained a major victory over the British at New Orleans in the War of 1812. Who was he?",
    "questionId": "b877ae8940231c2299a8cc5ce1e827b2",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Oregon",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Oregon",
      "Arizona",
      "California",
      "Nevada"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "As a result of victory in the Mexican War of 1846-48, the United States gained all of the following states EXCEPT this one.",
    "questionId": "5698d91cf182ee82668b568cabb2687d",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "slavery",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "slavery",
      "status of new western territories",
      "states rights",
      "tariffs"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What was the one irreconcilable issue between North and South that led to the American Civil War?",
    "questionId": "01c308c6a185eaafc79b85cafd1cf5d1",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Gettysburg",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Gettysburg",
      "Shiloh",
      "Second Bull Run",
      "Antietam"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "The Union victory in this battle, fought in July 1863, is generally considered the turning point of the American Civil War. After the battle President Lincoln made a memorable speech at the site of the battle. What was the battle?",
    "questionId": "88a7e5a683416c39c438648dd93d6010",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "US industrialization advanced rapidly.",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Blacks in the southern states were integrated into the southern population with very little conflict or discrimination.",
      "Native Americans (Indians) were generally treated fairly and territorial disputes were settled.",
      "US industrialization advanced rapidly.",
      "Laws were passed that greatly restricted European immigration into the US."
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which of the following is true about the United States in the period between the end of the Civil War in 1865 and the beginning of the 20th century?",
    "questionId": "6461e49198379472c703479bbd78dd00",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "President Wilson wanted to destroy communism.",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "German submarines began sinking US ships in 1917.",
      "The US had strong cultural and commercial ties with Britain and France.",
      "France and Britain were democratic and Germany was not.",
      "President Wilson wanted to destroy communism."
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which of the following was NOT a reason why the US entered World War One on the side of Britain and France?",
    "questionId": "ec6ec240d665bb2d4b3d74ce892fbeb5",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "alcoholic beverages",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "US joining any international organization",
      "alcoholic beverages",
      "prostitution",
      "same sex marriages"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In 1919 an amendment to the US Constitution (which was rescinded in 1933) prohibited which of the following?",
    "questionId": "f061234c70936789d0c55d03ce6b0bb7",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "All of these",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Programs to provide jobs by building roads, schools, dams, etc.",
      "The Securities and Exchange Commission to regulate the stock market",
      "Social Security that provided pensions for retired workers",
      "All of these"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In 1933 Franklin Roosevelt was elected president. He promised to bring a New Deal to Americans to bring recovery from the Great Depression and improve social conditions. Which of the following did his New Deal include?",
    "questionId": "edee84eab388df9b3f854af7c6b88834",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Midway",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Leyte Gulf",
      "Okinawa",
      "Singapore",
      "Midway"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "The Japanese defeat in this naval battle in the Pacific is generally considered to be the turning point of the Second World War.",
    "questionId": "d3a3570110bbe0200e6db66d868d077b",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "There was never any actual warfare in the Cold War.",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "There was never any actual warfare in the Cold War.",
      "It was partly a clash of very different ideologies.",
      "It began soon after World War Two ended, partly because of Soviet domination of Eastern Europe.",
      "Nuclear weapons were a threat to both sides in the Cold War."
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which of these statements is NOT true about the Cold War?",
    "questionId": "669ef06d676f3741bc819a7b3f04b5ee",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Cuba",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Germany",
      "North Korea",
      "China",
      "Cuba"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Many think that the closest the world came to nuclear war was in 1962 when President Kennedy demanded that the Soviets remove nuclear missiles they had recently placed in this country.",
    "questionId": "71239ce20018ddc0a0baf597e3c4cdfe",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "1932",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "1939",
      "1932",
      "1934",
      "1927"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Ole Kirk Christiansen, the founder of the LEGO Group, started producing wooden toys in what year?",
    "questionId": "2a51c53271bc0e34518499a2c26100ad",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Play Well",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Put Together",
      "Play Well",
      "Build Well",
      "Stack Well"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In 1934, Ole Kirk Christiansen named his toy-producing company LEGO, a word derived from the Danish phrase leg godt, which means what in English?",
    "questionId": "4211bc44a92f1cd7a23a4555ca2c27b5",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "1942",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "1945",
      "1944",
      "1942",
      "1940"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "During this year the Lego company, founded by Ole Kirk Christiansen, was devastated by a fire.",
    "questionId": "9c7d42370dd664168a9c4863a4cdbbb1",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "LEGO was the first company in Denmark to buy and use a plastic injection-molding machine for toys.",
    "questionId": "c1bdc747d355385f64bb600f8bc67bf8",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "1950",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "1952",
      "1949",
      "1950",
      "1947"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In what year did Godtfred Kirk Christiansen become Junior Vice President of the LEGO company?",
    "questionId": "cad587f5f5e59b733c395ff4f5642d13",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "LEGO System of Play",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "LEGO Building Set",
      "LEGO Toy Set of Building",
      "LEGO System of Play",
      "LEGO System"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the name of the revolutionary LEGO series of 28 sets and 8 vehicles, launched in 1955?",
    "questionId": "5bacd6220e9a239ea6fae3622fed6e5f",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In 1963, the LEGO company replaced the building substance for the bricks, cellulose acetate with acrylonitrile butadiene stryrene, which improved the color quality.",
    "questionId": "166c75052e956082b7cc899e35f807b2",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In 1989, the LEGO company released a new series, named Pirates.",
    "questionId": "a8ead510e608af7688ad50d76fd76dcb",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Gryffindor",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Ravenclaw",
      "Gryffindor",
      "Slytherin",
      "Hufflepuff"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which house of Hogwarts was fictional character Sirius Black in when he attended the famous school?",
    "questionId": "fae3664f0473497794c395a449258dcb",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "A dog",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "A wolf",
      "A dog",
      "A Deer",
      "A Rat"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Harry Potter character Sirius Black was an Animagi meaning that he could take the form of an animal. What animal could he emulate?",
    "questionId": "be6f196190134ff68fb394f1031e7140",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix the headquarters of the organization was in Sirius family home.",
    "questionId": "cc0628a8f4d0a9296f2444e8f91d79da",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Harry Potter and The Prisoner of Azkaban",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Harry Potter and The Sorcerers Stone",
      "Harry Potter and The Prisoner of Azkaban",
      "Harry potter and The Chamber of Secrets",
      "Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In which Harry Potter novel did Sirius Black make his first major appearance?",
    "questionId": "3674a0f3257804e622bbcadf6369dbe2",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "A motorcycle",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "A broomstick",
      "A motorcycle",
      "A Car",
      "A carpet"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What magical flying item of Sirius Black was given to Hagrid upon the knowledge of Harry Potters parents death?",
    "questionId": "a3e4fb2045dad5f23861618dee38c0b5",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Orion",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Orion",
      "Teodor",
      "Draco",
      "Rudolph"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What was the name of Sirius Blacks father in the Harry Potter series?",
    "questionId": "a7c57988d0168f6bb8652ae50067a457",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Sirius Black dies in the novel Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince.",
    "questionId": "f1f10c1067267c086aa1f37ed9176b14",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Potions",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Divination",
      "Potions",
      "Charms",
      "Astronomy"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which of the following classes was taught by Professor Snape in the Harry Potter series?",
    "questionId": "dc96bb43cc106a6bb70381150f4f3ff4",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "He was in love with Harrys mother.",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "He was half muggle.",
      "He killed Albus Dumbledore.",
      "He was in love with Harrys mother.",
      "He was Lord Voldemorts brother."
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What secret about Professor Snape was divulged in Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows, which is the final book in the series?",
    "questionId": "ffa8c8db4b3a6a6bceebf3a980b47031",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the Harry Potter series, Professor Snape became headmaster of Hogwarts after the death of Dumbledore.",
    "questionId": "135ee586737b73c7404670a8f12e77dd",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Doe",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Doe",
      "Dragon",
      "Wolf",
      "Snake"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What was Snapes patronus in the Harry Potter series?",
    "questionId": "550eaa2b4f0a0f9e2749b67702673457",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the final book of the Harry Potter series, Harry finally kills Snape.",
    "questionId": "ee73edc61787671bcc2dbc29ac71eb0a",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Defense Against the Dark Arts",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Care of magical Creatures",
      "Potions",
      "Divination",
      "Defense Against the Dark Arts"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the Harry Potter series, what was the teaching position most coveted by Professor Snape?",
    "questionId": "924fb32c244d8c14909a939391aba5ee",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the final book in the Harry Potter series, it is revealed that Harry names one of his sons after Snape.",
    "questionId": "65718546fb162aa8fac56465c6636bc4",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "true",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Fictional character Snape is the half-blood prince.",
    "questionId": "0123ceb521c4ff0ff82206ab3f7e7699",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Weatherby",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Rainlet",
      "Cloudy boy",
      "Weatherboy",
      "Weatherby"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What did Mr. Crouch from the Ministry of Magic call Percy in book 4 of the Harry Potter series?",
    "questionId": "d7e8cf9d360bbe4567c3174152b12728",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Professor Flitwick",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Professor Snape",
      "Professor Sprout",
      "Professor Quirrell",
      "Professor Flitwick"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "There were all types of enchantments guarding the Sorcerers Stone. Which teacher put the flying keys there to protect it in the first Harry Potter book?",
    "questionId": "4b2cb60d0e86e7239e2a88535626513c",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Books 3 and 4",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Books 3 and 5",
      "Books 3 and 4",
      "Books 4 and 5",
      "Books 3 and 6"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In which two books did Harry Potter make a Patronus because he thought he saw a dementor, even though it was not really a dementor?",
    "questionId": "ebd8924eb63222993053a12a3b87f727",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the sixth book of the Harry Potter series, Professor Slughorn became the Head of Slytherin.",
    "questionId": "0571704e1968f398b9e7d256d25953af",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "The character of Sirius Black is mentioned in the book Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban for the first time.",
    "questionId": "f8339f5ba312d399783aaf926e46fccd",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Harry Potter",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Tom Riddle",
      "Harry Potter",
      "Pansy Parkinson",
      "Ron Weasley"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which of the following Harry Potter characters is not a prefect?",
    "questionId": "f0f9816bff27293b447fec9d4a717d26",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Ginny",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Cho",
      "No one",
      "Ginny",
      "Hermione"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which of these characters does Harry kiss in Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince?",
    "questionId": "241f6fc8ca2a547451a58cf4e0230962",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Lavender Brown and Ron Won Won Weasley start going out in chapter 9 of Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince.",
    "questionId": "69726d13acdd8d50040edd0b9889f6cc",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Amelia Bones",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Kingsley Shackelbolt",
      "Stubby Boardman",
      "Percival Wulfricshire",
      "Amelia Bones"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What previously mentioned character was killed in chapter 1 of Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince?",
    "questionId": "c868b5540a92e9eacf4e6f9c62d6d17b",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince, Cho Chang waves to Harry once but then hurries away with Marietta.",
    "questionId": "a529382faf95845156fa7e38395bbed8",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "A love potion",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "A love potion",
      "A love spell",
      "An imperious curse",
      "A potion and spell"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What does Merope supposedly use to make Tom Riddle Sr. fall in love with her in Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince?",
    "questionId": "289d4ccf5ad052dc2e44d453991ec8df",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "false",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In Harry Potter and The Half-Blood Prince, Dumbledore's blood is the only blood used in the cavern by the sea where the horcrux is hidden.",
    "questionId": "2986a22b47d78ab3d7ee67e912f624fd",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Inferi",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Inferi",
      "Infery",
      "Infreri",
      "Infrery"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the book Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince, a corpse that is re-animated but isn\u2019t alive is called what?",
    "questionId": "85edc2b5845faeef5f009bdb8bc210dd",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Harry destroyed two Horcruxes in Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince.",
    "questionId": "f3576997d1076a085674702d953ec065",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Snakes",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Snakes",
      "Wolves",
      "Spiders",
      "Centaurs"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Lord Voldemort had the ability to talk to these creatures.",
    "questionId": "b454e69e3e72570fa1582c85d3310c12",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Tom",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "John",
      "Michael",
      "Tom",
      "Ron"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is Lord Voldemorts real first name?",
    "questionId": "c985a153f1c1d86c31357728a2d2687c",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Diary",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Sword",
      "Stone",
      "Diary",
      "Ring"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What was the very first of Lord Voldemorts horcruxes to appear in the Harry Potter series of books?",
    "questionId": "4389719ed78a412a8be91fbb9a066f7c",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Slytherin",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Ravenclaw",
      "Huffelpuff",
      "Slytherin",
      "Gryffendore"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which of these Hogwarts founders was Lord Voldemorts ancestor?",
    "questionId": "cda8cdebe7ff7bb6942b73affe4888a2",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Lord Voldemort is related to Harry Potter.",
    "questionId": "c30dc284c3696635730fff89d50aa9a9",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Hagrid",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Tonks",
      "Severus Snape",
      "Hagrid",
      "Professor Lupin"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which of these characters does Voldemort NOT kill in the final Harry Potter book Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows?",
    "questionId": "89bd445578faa7ee2784d5a5bdfad20b",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Harry Potter defeats and kills Lord Voldemort in the final Harry Potter book.",
    "questionId": "99eebb1021f4ad3833796074896a9569",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Peter and Wendy",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Alices Adventures in Wonderland",
      "Peter and Wendy",
      "Pinocchio",
      "Pippi Longstocking"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What childrens novel features Neverland, the magical island where people cease to age?",
    "questionId": "d34fc7b746526b1d2f269c8433129a17",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Both of these",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Both of these",
      "Pinocchio",
      "None of these",
      "Buratino"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What classic fictional character is a long-nosed wooden puppet?",
    "questionId": "4a5f0f51e76c0fcdcc544e20aa8faf89",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "the Chief Weasel",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "the Queen of Hearts",
      "the Mock Turtle",
      "the March Hare",
      "the Chief Weasel"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which of the following is not a character from Lewis Carrolls 1865 novel Alices Adventures in Wonderland?",
    "questionId": "c2ce9083a8463f23922259e908b322aa",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "the Fox",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "the Fox",
      "the Snake",
      "the Lamplighter",
      "the Rose"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What character from Antoine de Saint-Exup\u00e9rys novella, The Little Prince, utters these famous lines that sum up the essence of the book: One cannot see well except with the heart, the essential is invisible to the eyes.?",
    "questionId": "85eea4751d642a25da1a738a2f5798e1",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Madonna Louise Ciccone",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Theodor Seuss Geisel",
      "Helen Beatrix Potter",
      "Madonna Louise Ciccone",
      "Dorothy Gladys Smith"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the birth name of the author who penned The English Roses, a childrens book that follows the lives of four girls?",
    "questionId": "1fe3e1a6484c43229bd24eff28af00d2",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "A. A. Milne",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "C. S. Lewis",
      "Lemony Snicket",
      "A. A. Milne",
      "Lewis Carroll"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What childrens book author named one of his central characters after his son?",
    "questionId": "d5d0a3dfd84ad182633984d37604b468",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Mulan",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "One Hundred and One Dalmatians",
      "The Many Adventures of Winnie the Pooh",
      "Mulan",
      "Bambi"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which of these Disney animated features is not based on a book written by an European author?",
    "questionId": "9343380a35dd611b2ff21e5444ceabea",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Anne of Green Gables",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Little House in the Big Woods",
      "Anne of Green Gables",
      "Little Women",
      "Heidi"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What best-selling novel tells the story of an orphan girl adopted by middle-aged siblings, Marilla and Matthew Cuthbert?",
    "questionId": "b9e66bd7bdf8780ca7bfac5e85a67051",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Pippi",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Karlsson",
      "Pippi",
      "Ronia",
      "Lucy Pevensie"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "This extraordinary strong, red-haired fictional character lives in Villa Villekula with a monkey, named Mr. Nilsson.",
    "questionId": "c7b6c47c7733f26e01368f7b759dfc07",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Mowgly, Raksha - Edgar Rice Burroughs",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Lucy Pevensie, Caspian - C. S. Lewis",
      "Mowgly, Raksha - Edgar Rice Burroughs",
      "Joe Harper, Becky Thatcher  - Mark Twain",
      "Meg March, Amy March - Louisa May Alcott"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which characters are not correctly matched with the authors who created them?",
    "questionId": "90abb9783c8940d903bb0b8ab00d0b0c",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows, Severus Snape was headmaster for a period of time.",
    "questionId": "0101bfa24be583d28875635ea2f75bf5",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "He discovered something important.",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "He discovered something important.",
      "He forgot what time it was.",
      "He does not like meetings.",
      "He was teaching."
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the first chapter of Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows, why was Snape late for a meeting with Lord Voldemort?",
    "questionId": "756f96f5ef3b098ec002e535cbd0dd25",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Harry got cut by a fragment of a mirror.",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Harry got cut by a fragment of a mirror.",
      "Dudley put a cup of tea right behind Harrys door and Harry stepped on it.",
      "Dudley put a glass of water behind Harrys door and Harry stepped on it.",
      "Harry bit his lip."
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "The first sentence in the second chapter in Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows is Harry was bleeding. Why is that so?",
    "questionId": "ef5289e3cc652cd6391a8323a0f8e5ff",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Magical Mirror",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Resurrection Stone",
      "Magical Mirror",
      "Elder Wand",
      "Invisibility Cloak"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT a Deathly Hallow?",
    "questionId": "6e18efbf2af3a69896a120487c17728c",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "George",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Ron",
      "Fred",
      "Bill",
      "George"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which Weasley boy got his ear cut off in the last book of the Harry Potter series?",
    "questionId": "e8a7d7b40d314080676a657ab110b02c",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Vernon Dudley",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Dudley Dursley",
      "Vernon Dursley",
      "Dudley Vernon",
      "Vernon Dudley"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What did Harry Potter say that his name was when he, Ron, and Hermione got caught by a gang of Snatchers in Harry Potter and the Deadly Hallows?",
    "questionId": "a17ee4067cf8fa8cc71b51ef71507e70",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "8",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "6",
      "8",
      "5",
      "7"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "If you add 3 to 5, what would be the result?",
    "questionId": "9324247819a3bd76546c1a1ca88b6073",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "$2.00",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "$2.25",
      "$1.50",
      "$1.00",
      "$2.00"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "If Jane had $3.00 and went to the store and bought a yo yo for $1.00, how much would Jane have left?",
    "questionId": "d22cec7526c71cbab1589895c0c8ded7",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "15",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "14",
      "15",
      "13",
      "16"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the correct solution to this problem: 16 - 4 + 3 =?",
    "questionId": "eba3b5f00c3bc134606e434dd37b2a81",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "7 dollars",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "8 dollars",
      "3 dollars",
      "7 dollars",
      "5 dollars"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "If T.J. went to the circus with 10 dollars and bought some fruit snacks for 3 dollars, how much money would T. J. then have left over?",
    "questionId": "682abf4fbc1d392906905d261b645925",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "5 dollars",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "5 dollars",
      "10 dollars",
      "8 dollars",
      "15 dollars"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "If Lindsay had $20.00 and bought 3 tickets to the Mets game, how much money would Lindsay have left if each ticket cost 5 dollars?",
    "questionId": "d126032b678b519ad227f19a1bfca0ae",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "3",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "3",
      "4",
      "2",
      "1"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "If Donna bought 5 blowpop lollipops from the candy store and gave her friend 2 of them, how many blowpops would Donna then have?",
    "questionId": "e549bec7bec9e10621ea17f4c165582d",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "12",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "12",
      "6",
      "18",
      "10"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "How many inches are there in a foot?",
    "questionId": "f84b7817271c209ec2975a5240c0c27f",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "13",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "14",
      "13",
      "12",
      "11"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "If Anthony had 8 apples, 2 oranges and 3 pears, how many pieces of fruit does Anthony have altogether?",
    "questionId": "ca2f0b0d9110f5b0fd406cb70c114853",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "9",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "8",
      "9",
      "7",
      "6"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the solution to this problem 12-3=?",
    "questionId": "2e4e9f1c83ea3646e28d49f530a7e873",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "5 dollars",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "40 dollars",
      "6 dollars",
      "4 dollars",
      "5 dollars"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Amanda went to the book store to buy some books. Her mom gave her a $10 bill. She bought two books that cost $2.00 each and a bookmark that cost $1.00. How much change did Amanda give her mother when she got home?",
    "questionId": "afdf554d273076721c5d394b7c3bdc0c",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "He transformed into a dog.",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "None of these",
      "He was able to contact his cousin Bellatrix who helped him escape from Azkaban.",
      "He transformed into a dog.",
      "He was able to control one of the dementors."
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "How did Sirius Black escape from Azkaban, the wizard prison in the third book of the Harry Poter series?",
    "questionId": "de30ead7cac9f697081f64710fd02205",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Remus Lupin",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Severus Snape",
      "Remus Lupin",
      "Dolores Umbridge",
      "Alastor Mad-Eye Moody"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Who is the new Defense Against the Dark Arts teacher in Harry Potters third year at Hogwarts?",
    "questionId": "85a329c99866ef148cff3a3ccbf5b385",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Fictional character Remus Lupin was an animagus.",
    "questionId": "a0cb4b84ff14ee15f126f1935402322c",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Expecto Patronum",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Expelliarmus",
      "Impedimenta",
      "Wingardium Leviosa",
      "Expecto Patronum"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the spell incantation for conjuring a Patronus in the Harry Potter books?",
    "questionId": "897227337502b3c1e7ca2a3541f8c0b5",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Care of Magical Creatures",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Care of Magical Creatures",
      "Potions",
      "Transfiguration",
      "Defense Against the Dark Arts"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban, Rubeus Hagrid was appointed by Headmaster Albus Dumbledore as the new teacher of what subject?",
    "questionId": "71cf51e45f89261c440ad65fb7f4cff0",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Fred and George",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Fred and George",
      "Remus Lupin",
      "Argus Filch",
      "Rubeus Hagrid"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Who gave the Marauders Map to Harry in Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban?",
    "questionId": "91fd54b1573f97ec4e341fa5c10961c9",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "The Shrieking Shack, depicted in the Harry Potter books, was considered to be the most haunted place in Great Britain.",
    "questionId": "c6301a702f39c04146f20ea5b1b77248",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Even without a permission slip, Harry Potter was able to go to Hogsmeade with Ron and Hermione during certain weekends.",
    "questionId": "530d8d191606f1e705bb001bf1ae6113",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Britney Spears",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Nikki DeLoach",
      "Britney Spears",
      "Justin Timberlake",
      "JC Chasez"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In 2000, this Mouseketeer became the youngest person to be both host and musical guest on Saturday Night Live.",
    "questionId": "4a7e7d9d28c16aa867411965863b35b6",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Emerald Cove",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "The Party",
      "Spin and Marty",
      "Emerald Cove",
      "The Hardy Boys"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Name the weekly ten-minute drama on the All-New Mickey Mouse Club starring Tony Lucca, Keri Russel and JC Chasez?",
    "questionId": "221dded9ed9fa1dbbcc2710981627417",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "An oil painting",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "An oil painting",
      "Amelia Bones",
      "None of these",
      "Herbert Chorley"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince, who delivered the Prime Minister the message that the Minister of Magic had sent?",
    "questionId": "0956938b7767295ac4913f8d8ec0198e",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince, The Minister of Magic came only once to visit the Prime Minister.",
    "questionId": "d17113777a0e7896f1540767cc9f5626",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Dragon blood",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Pumpkin juice",
      "Dragon blood",
      "Dwarf blood",
      "Ink"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What was spattered over the wallpaper on Professor Slughorns house in Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince?",
    "questionId": "5bfc0b469d2fc00c812c0fb58540dfdc",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Luna Lovegoods father",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Luna Lovegood",
      "Luna Lovegoods uncle",
      "Ron Weasley",
      "Luna Lovegoods father"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Who wrote the magazine named Quibbler in the Half-Blood Prince?",
    "questionId": "8e485f6f7441ed00a232732ef75bc5f2",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Sectumsempra",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Alohomora",
      "Sectumsempra",
      "None of these",
      "Felix Felicis"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What was the name of spell that Harry used on Malfoy in Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince?",
    "questionId": "907413461eba4a223e9d85e84cc504fd",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "true",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Hermione and Ron secretly like each other in the sixth book of the Harry Potter series.",
    "questionId": "9e2d2750538b10a43c7a01b791d1c260",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Harry - Ginny",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Harry - Ginny",
      "Harry - Hermione",
      "Harry - Cho",
      "None of these"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the sixth book of the Harry Potter series, which of the following characters eventually formed a couple?",
    "questionId": "a1402e991de181a70da57f93f104fcf9",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "purple",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "blue",
      "purple",
      "red",
      "black"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What color was Quirrels turban in the Harry Potter books?",
    "questionId": "22626a12850700eb64a83b7136c9c310",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Harry Potters middle name is James.",
    "questionId": "5fec347a16ce6b613234fae588f22412",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "So Lupin could come to school",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "So Harry and Ron would have something to run into with the flying car",
      "The students could have shade",
      "So Lupin could come to school",
      "To protect the school"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Why was the womping willow planted in the Harry Potter books?",
    "questionId": "8b67ecf4f71f9acfa28309fc8737f01d",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "His father bought brooms for the whole team",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "He was the only candidate.",
      "He was actually good enough.",
      "His father bought brooms for the whole team",
      "He shot a man in Reno just to watch him die."
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "How does Malfoy join the Slytherin quidditch team?",
    "questionId": "7a35ac01b979fef20a860a3e051ab33d",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "He is Harrys Godfather.",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "He is Harrys Godfather.",
      "He is Harrys uncle.",
      "He is Harrys cousin.",
      "He is Harrys half-brother."
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "How is Sirius related to Harry Potter?",
    "questionId": "723d1b7a188948c51a9bd372ebed664f",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Snape",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Lupin",
      "Trelawny",
      "McGonagall",
      "Snape"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Who is the teacher in the Harry Potter books that is made fun of by the Marauders map?",
    "questionId": "9ad778e8b534c67373f1bc371a6d5db8",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "J.K. Rowling",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "J.R. Rowling",
      "C.S. Lewis",
      "J.K. Rowling",
      "J.R. Tolkien"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Who wrote the Harry Potter series of books?",
    "questionId": "585f225072c7fdea3e3773c239a6d6da",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Swan and Otter",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Swan and Otter",
      "Stag and Frog",
      "Frog and Otter",
      "Frog and Swan"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What were Hermiones and Chos patronus forms in the Harry Potter books?",
    "questionId": "cc8d3a5eccfaa169184ed57fe0828a0e",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Fictional characters Ron Weasley and Harry Potter met on the Hogwarts Express.",
    "questionId": "3c61d67e261e279a3bf4bf60d297fca3",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Every headmaster/headmistress of the fictional Hogwarts school has had the same office.",
    "questionId": "a16225f7b46449bb611e9a10f457e7f3",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "bezoar",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "antidote to love potions",
      "wand",
      "bezoar",
      "boggart"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What magical object did Harry Potter use to save Ron from poisoning?",
    "questionId": "441039b6bc6a9315d86f8115fd878fab",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Fictional character Mr. Weasley was on guard duty when the basilisk attacked him.",
    "questionId": "761a07f67d5b83d342d661dc8047d043",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "false",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Fictional character Ron Weasley lives at 12, Grimmauld Place.",
    "questionId": "5646b96563689096c30a74f2c144e3c6",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince",
      "Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix.",
      "Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban",
      "Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In what Harry Potter book did the Brockdale Bridge collapse?",
    "questionId": "546ee7c9eb5a7177e7b39cc2983df6a3",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Fictional characters Fred and George Weasley get kicked out of Hogwarts.",
    "questionId": "52ca150ee7d5faf970dfe4f0a923822b",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Albus Dumbledore",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Phineas Nigeallus",
      "Minevera McGonagall",
      "Severus Snape",
      "Albus Dumbledore"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Who is Headmaster at Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry in books 1-6 of the Harry Potter series?",
    "questionId": "8bd27c40e28b0fe5132b165268454b76",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "McGonagall",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Snape",
      "McGonagall",
      "Lupin",
      "Trelawney"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Who is head of the fictional Gryffindor house?",
    "questionId": "8b5847f2088d846d7ee084589c479715",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Fictional character Professor Snape is head of Ravenclaw house.",
    "questionId": "0fdc43cc9bc9785cb006864ba7df2f78",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "false",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Flitwick is head of Hufflepuff house in the Harry Potter series of books.",
    "questionId": "b0738d861b2ed47168709deabcb19d57",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Slughorn",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Slughorn",
      "McGonagal",
      "Sprout",
      "Snape"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Who is head of Slytherin house in the book Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows?",
    "questionId": "e341e2cf79200024309bc79c101d3d64",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The Gray Lady",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Sprout",
      "The Bloody Baron",
      "The Gray Lady",
      "Flitwick"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Who is the ghost of Ravenclaw in the Harry Potter books?",
    "questionId": "c0a97051a7985ed5c213831cba22fcf5",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Professor Sprout is head of Hufflepuff, one of the fictional Hogwarts houses.",
    "questionId": "0e80006033fa8a5faa15c6851109f385",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Nearly Headless Nick",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Moaning Myrtle",
      "The Gray Lady",
      "The Bloody Baron",
      "Nearly Headless Nick"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Who is the Gryffindor ghost in the Harry Potter books?",
    "questionId": "9c9661fd433f15e70f8131feb6f8c8e5",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the Harry Potter books, the Bloody Baron is Slytherins ghost.",
    "questionId": "8792b392efa8b72f01f6d2104c75500a",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "true",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Harry Potter is a member of Gryffindor house.",
    "questionId": "d858171016b7fc4d14fe177812ba1367",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "12",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "12",
      "7",
      "14",
      "71"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the square root of 144?",
    "questionId": "a2b39867ba62aaec344b96c3be2e17ee",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Devils Snare, keys, chessboard, potions",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Keys, Devils Snare, chessboard, potions",
      "Chessboard, keys, Devils Snare, potions",
      "Devils Snare, chessboard, keys, potions",
      "Devils Snare, keys, chessboard, potions"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the first book of the Harry Potter series, when Harry, Ron and Hermione went into the restricted corridor, what was the order of the obstacles to get to Quirrell?",
    "questionId": "f41b5aa20d851734b9d7fc5cc7abf33d",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "a black dog",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "a Dachshund",
      "a black dog",
      "a black cat",
      "a yellow cat"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What shape does Sirius Blacks Animagus take in the 3rd book of the Harry Potter series?",
    "questionId": "c293809582a33dce43254c46d1ba7062",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "number 12, Grimmauld place",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "number 19, Grimmauld place",
      "number 15, Grimmauld place",
      "number 13, Grimmauld place",
      "number 12, Grimmauld place"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the address of the Order of the Phoenix headquarters in the Harry Potter novels?",
    "questionId": "9d1fd8a542ad5009b9fdf3bce1a40b08",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "an orphanage",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "an ordinary house",
      "an run-down shack",
      "a school bus",
      "an orphanage"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Where did fictional character Tom Riddle (Voldemort) live before going to live and study at Hogwarts?",
    "questionId": "2def2b16c4264acd536a1d489645d4d4",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "54",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "51",
      "53",
      "54",
      "55"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "How many people died at the fictional battle of Hogwarts?",
    "questionId": "73bbe4aedb41b285c89bce5b331d281d",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "true",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Harry Potter married Ginny Weasley.",
    "questionId": "d6893fa61fd7f26defd1fb3b1018d119",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "All the books of the Harry Potter series are set in England and Scotland.",
    "questionId": "f92a9ce129629a7ed31847d18d353a7b",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "4",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "1",
      "3",
      "2",
      "4"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "How many champions names came out of the fictional Goblet of Fire?",
    "questionId": "c0da8ca6ed09154675a16e294c3e8a9b",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Count Olaf",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Madam Lulu.",
      "Aunt Josephine",
      "Esme Squalor",
      "Count Olaf"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Who was the first guardian to whom the Baudelaires were sent in A Series of Unfortunate Events?",
    "questionId": "e35a390fe6e0dc36483098055b1536bd",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the novel The Penultimate Peril, Jaques Snicket was one of the two people who signed into the hotel as J.S..",
    "questionId": "b99721334c3a4b998ceabe39fa53bcfc",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Esme Squalor",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Hector",
      "Jerome Squalor",
      "Uncle Monty",
      "Esme Squalor"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which character from A Series of Unfortunate Events said that orphans were in?",
    "questionId": "9be07c4b4930409a4922f5cc451316b0",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The King of Arizona",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "The King of Arizona",
      "The President of Nepal",
      "The Prime Minister of New York",
      "The Grand Admiral of Canada"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which of the following were mentioned in the book The Ersatz Elevator?",
    "questionId": "dcb2da659b7a0abd764e9a1a4bc57fac",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Isadora Quagmire",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Uncle Monty",
      "Duncan Quagmire",
      "Kit Snicket",
      "Isadora Quagmire"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which of the following fictional characters, depicted by Lemony Snicket, is a poet?",
    "questionId": "f194f3244c8508d5790164e7a6b7dac1",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Sirs",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Phils",
      "Beatrices",
      "Carmelita Spats",
      "Sirs"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In A Series of Unfortunate Events, whose head was always hidden behind a cloud of smoke?",
    "questionId": "121f9e934fba5fd6cc2f01dc38089976",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "false",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the second book of A Series of Unfortunate Events, Count Olaf tricked the Baudelaires into thinking he was really Stephano.",
    "questionId": "23a67a8ee3ece54e55d09da2219defab",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The Vile Village",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "The Miserable Mill",
      "The Bad Beginning",
      "The Vile Village",
      "The Penultimate Peril"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In which of Lemony Snickets books does Jaques Snicket die?",
    "questionId": "ce7d7629a52ad1282a88a8383eb1279a",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In A Series of Unfortunate Events, Klaus was the best inventor out of all the Baudelaires.",
    "questionId": "95c3f5b40aea98e37fb9aa5b5cb64251",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Wubbzy",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Willard",
      "Wanker",
      "Hank",
      "Wubbzy"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "This character is in a show with his two friends, Widget and Walden. He is yellow with a long, springy tail, and greets people by saying, Wow wow.",
    "questionId": "8f0d6aa533e2d54bef5991cfc01c9eb0",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "The show Dora the Explorer features a little girl who goes on all sorts of adventures with her friend, Tico the Dog.",
    "questionId": "3bb9fdcd47d5c9411baa2955ceb3a767",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Yo Gabba Gabba!",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Yo Pinky Dinky!",
      "Yo Diddle Diddle",
      "Yo Mama Jama",
      "Yo Gabba Gabba!"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "This show features characters with offbeat names like Muno, Foofa, Brobee, Toodee, Plex, and DJ Lance.",
    "questionId": "99e7e21757c161c4643faaea84b2a6dd",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Ruby",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Pearl",
      "Fluff",
      "Louise",
      "Ruby"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "A TV show that debuted in 2002 features 2 bunnies. Max is a 3 year-old bunny that is always doing something to distract his sister, although he always manages to help her in the end. What is his sisters name?",
    "questionId": "b114252a7e009fd1099b5f8712398e51",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Lazy Town",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Sleepy Town",
      "Lazy Town",
      "Active Town",
      "Funky Town"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "This show features an active hero named Sportacus, who uses exercise and good nutrition to thwart the schemes of the slothful Robbie Rotten. Most of the characters in this show are puppets.",
    "questionId": "97a132c9b9d6b0b30041dfc540e8938a",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Steve and Joe",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Stan and Stu",
      "Steve and Joe",
      "Larry and Jake",
      "Jack and Jim"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "The show Blues Clues featured 2 different hosts during its run. What were their names?",
    "questionId": "f7f92ea086c3f54ab452ed8c7f3dca51",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The Backyardigans",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "The Backyardamals",
      "The Backyardigans",
      "The Backyard Gang",
      "The Backyard Band"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "This show follows Pablo the Penguin, Tyrone the Moose, Tasha the Hippopotamus, Austin the Kangaroo, and Uniqua on their imaginary adventures in the backyard.",
    "questionId": "3bd0173fa20f4c40463e7b004a88ea20",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Ni Hao, Kai-Lan",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Ni Hao, Kai-Lan",
      "Ni Hao, Karen Chau",
      "Ni Hao, Yeoh-La",
      "Ni Hao, Shu-Shu"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "This show centers around a young girl, who speaks English and Chinese, and teaches problem solving. Other characters featured on the show are the girls grandfather,  Ye Ye, and her friends Rintoo, Tolee, Hoho, and Lulu.",
    "questionId": "901037e5b3fbb6cb691c842e24c1d84f",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The Wonder Pets",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "The Teamwork Trio",
      "The Super Squirrels",
      "The Wonder Pets",
      "The Amazing Animals"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Linny, Tuck, and Ming MIng too! These schoolhouse animals are always using teamwork to save baby animals in trouble.",
    "questionId": "ed2b4eb235fc918fc73ba756e9496424",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Diego",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Marco",
      "Diego",
      "Juan",
      "Luis"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "This young boy started off in his cousin Dora the Explorers show, but soon received his own show. He is an animal rescuer, along with his sister, Alicia.",
    "questionId": "6de61d36a4ec8baa3ad6a638227dd605",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Experiment House",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Educational High School",
      "Experiment House",
      "English School for Grammar",
      "Experimentation Hall"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In The Silver Chair, Eustace Scrubb returns to Narnia with his schoolmate Jill Pole, who attends what school with him?",
    "questionId": "78a267efc8260d9364c4fc4c48b1ecd9",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "He looses his balance and falls",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Jill gives him a hug",
      "He looses his balance and falls",
      "He is attacked by a lion",
      "Nothing"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What happens to Eustace as a result of Jills showing off at the edge of the cliff in the book The Silver Chair?",
    "questionId": "700770f4c855dbf7d63cc4bcf473fa23",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "To find the Prince Rilian, who has been missing for ten years",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "To kill the evil Green Witch, who has terrorized Narnia for a decade",
      "To prevent an attack from the underworld upon Narnia",
      "To free the talking beasts of Narnia from the tyranny of the Giants",
      "To find the Prince Rilian, who has been missing for ten years"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the novel The Silver Chair, Aslan gives Jill and Eustace a task and four signs to help them find the way. What is the task?",
    "questionId": "45b79e7275e3bb785f2f7f8c752bf701",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Caspian",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Reepicheep",
      "Edmund",
      "Drinian",
      "Caspian"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "The first of the signs given to Jill by Aslan in The Silver Chair was that Eustace was to see an old friend. Who did that old friend turn out to be?",
    "questionId": "58504800a0624b2e2ae9df16d3f57e04",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Owl",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Parakeet",
      "Gryphon",
      "Owl",
      "Eagle"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What sort of creature is Glimfeather, who helps Eustace and Jill get started on their journey in The Silver Chair?",
    "questionId": "e0b996207973a435b8e1bc1156d55c36",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "He is a pessimist, but is usually proved wrong",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "He is an optimist and is usually proved wrong",
      "He is an optimist, but is usually proved right",
      "He is a pessimist and is usually proved right",
      "He is a pessimist, but is usually proved wrong"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which of the following statements most correctly describes Puddleglum the Marsh-Wiggles outlook on life in C.S. Lewiss book The Silver Chair?",
    "questionId": "a778de0249901e551a304736b0183d4d",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "They are allowed entry and are given food, warm drink and beds.",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "They are captured by the Giants and thrown into cages.",
      "They are turned away by the Giants that live there and forced to sleep out in the cold.",
      "Nobody answers.",
      "They are allowed entry and are given food, warm drink and beds."
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What happens to Eustace, Jill and Puddleglum in The Silver Chair, when they knock on the gate of the Giant city of Harfang?",
    "questionId": "cdf2552c92b8074e2e8451f08e7e32bf",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Under Me",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Have Faith",
      "Trust Me",
      "Never Surrender",
      "Under Me"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In The Silver Chair, Jill has a dream in which she sees what two words out of the window of her room?",
    "questionId": "5a36b45b758360073fe79b182ca969f7",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Father Time",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Father Christmas",
      "Father Time",
      "Mother Earth",
      "Mother Nature"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "When Jill, Eustace and Puddleglum reach the Underworld, in The Silver Chair, they pass a large person sleeping and are told that this is who?",
    "questionId": "96b3205acee976219efa6e9c1eb2fc24",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "He remembers who he is and must be tied to a Silver Chair to prevent his escape",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "He forgets who he is and goes on a murderous rampage",
      "He enters the world of dreams and comes back with ingredients for the Witchs potions",
      "He relives the death of his mother through the eyes of the serpent that killed her",
      "He remembers who he is and must be tied to a Silver Chair to prevent his escape"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In The Silver Chair, Prince Rilian is found to be under the enchantment of the Green Witch.  What happens to Rilian for one hour each night under the Witchs spell?",
    "questionId": "3333de218b81ffce7fa874cdd598aeb0",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "in the name of Aslan",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "in the name of the White Witch",
      "in the name of God",
      "in the name of Aslan",
      "in the name of the Green Witch"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the Silver Chair, Eustace, Jill and Puddleglum rescue Rilian from the Silver Chair after he begs them to do it in whose name?",
    "questionId": "4084cdbfdc5173dc77c9baab36b69cd2",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Puddleglum",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Prince Rilian",
      "Eustace",
      "Jill",
      "Puddleglum"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which character in The Silver Chair burns his foot while putting out a magical fire created by the Green Witch?",
    "questionId": "e8bac5b77fd3b421fa7683653bcab993",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Centaur",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Unicorn",
      "Gryphon",
      "Centaur",
      "Pegasus"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In The Silver Chair, Jill and Eustace are allowed the privilege to ride what creature, which is most often too proud to be ridden?",
    "questionId": "ccde407429be98dc596c9f28e9e51841",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Caspian",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Aslan",
      "Rilian",
      "Caspian",
      "Puddleglum"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which character from the book The Silver Chair accompanies Jill and Eustace back to their own world when Aslan sends them out of his country?",
    "questionId": "3c6c9242176ac985d564facc77f82f10",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Daniel Radcliffe",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Daniel Fancliff",
      "Daniel Radcliffe",
      "None of these",
      "Wayne Knight"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the name of the actor who portrayed Harry Potter?",
    "questionId": "d0f86c93039081a4ee2ce34a19c6c985",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Cho Chang was Harry Potters girlfriend.",
    "questionId": "fa8ab566b41ae41acedb007b00397979",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "None of these",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Professor Snape",
      "None of these",
      "Professor Lupin",
      "Professor Umbridge"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What was the name of the DADA teacher in Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows?",
    "questionId": "0fe5986929e0d212894f85928515e20b",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Potterwatch",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "none of these",
      "Potterwatch",
      "The Daily Prophet",
      "The Quibler"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the name of the anti-Ministry of Magic radio station in Harry Potter and the Deadly Hallows?",
    "questionId": "c8fd79d3f690f9a1b1f1d4f8787d57dc",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "7",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "6",
      "4",
      "7",
      "5"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "How many books are in the Harry Potter series?",
    "questionId": "e37b692975cb2ce0d21f989cad7eef62",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "true",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Harry Potter's parents died on Halloween.",
    "questionId": "9ba5c2675310de6c3328d7d1d7e96797",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "He didnt work.",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "none of these",
      "He didnt work.",
      "minister of magic",
      "quidditch player"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What was the job of Harry Potters dad?",
    "questionId": "d1cbb596ba2ddb593d8afacc8998f1ed",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Cousin",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Nephew",
      "Uncle",
      "Cousin",
      "Brother"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In The Voyage of the Dawn Treader, Lucy and Edmund Pevensie return to Narnia along with a boy named Eustace. What relation is Eustace to Lucy and Edmund?",
    "questionId": "a058d4dfe32334be5a7387ce76c0376e",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "A painting",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "A looking glass",
      "A doorway",
      "A painting",
      "A wardrobe"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In The Voyage of the Dawn Treader, the three children travel to Narnia by what magical object?",
    "questionId": "4dbfff1ea02a99e7dee93b791241a1bb",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Seven Lords of Narnia banished by Caspians uncle, Miraz",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "A wife for Caspian to make Queen of Narnia",
      "Queen Susans horn",
      "Seven Lords of Narnia banished by Caspians uncle, Miraz",
      "Five Rings of Power created by Aslan"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the third book of the Chronicles of Narnia, the three children are rescued from the sea by Caspian and the crew of the Dawn Treader, who are on a voyage east from Narnia to find what?",
    "questionId": "6aad76a8eb2fef1b3fb90b0b5114f83a",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Swinging him around by his tail",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Kicking him into the water",
      "Stealing his ration of cheese",
      "Swinging him around by his tail",
      "Insulting the honor of his mother"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "At the beginning of the voyage, depicted in The Voyage of the Dawn Treader, Eustace is a nuisance to all aboard the Dawn Treader, including Reepicheep the mouse, whom he greatly offends by doing what?",
    "questionId": "63dd0513d73d18989c3d7aedd188c397",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Slave Traders",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Castaways",
      "Pirates",
      "Ghosts",
      "Slave Traders"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "While walking across the island of Felimath, featured in the book The Voyage of the Dawn Treader, Caspian, Reepicheep and the three children come across a band of men who they discover to be what?",
    "questionId": "47b390aae31b1ea5c644a3c672a53c6d",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Deathwater Island",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Tapwater Island",
      "Clearwater Island",
      "Goldwater Island",
      "Deathwater Island"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What name do the voyagers in The Voyage of the Dawn Treader give to the island on which they find the armor and sword of Lord Restimar lying beside a small pool of clear water?",
    "questionId": "95d950c2a222152679aaa828b9335c5c",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "They had only one foot",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "They had only one foot",
      "They had only one eye",
      "They had only one nostril",
      "They had only one hand"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "The Duffers, described in The Voyage of the Dawn Treader, have made themselves invisible and wish Lucy to help them become visible again. What was strange about the Duffers?",
    "questionId": "80a7ef49afcaa0e4eefaed357263c055",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Albatross",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Dolphin",
      "Lion",
      "Lightning Bug",
      "Albatross"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "As the ship voyages past Magician Coriakins island, the voyagers in the novel The Voyage of the Dawn Treader come across an island surrounded by a shroud of utter darkness. After entering this shroud, what type of animal sheds light to help them escape?",
    "questionId": "6073df14bc7c3851e95da9e0823a1b08",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Touching the stone knife laying on the table",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Eating the fruit from the banquet table",
      "Drinking the wine from the flagon on the table",
      "Insulting the daughter of the Lord of the island",
      "Touching the stone knife laying on the table"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In The Voyage of the Dawn Treader, after rescuing Lord Rhoop, the voyagers land upon another island where they find a large banquet table and three Lords of Narnia, each in an enchanted sleep due to what?",
    "questionId": "79e89d614f1e11717f70abfad7061ba4",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Lilies",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Foam",
      "Ice",
      "Frosting",
      "Lilies"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Sailing past Ramandus island, the voyagers from The Voyage of the Dawn Treader spot a white mass on the horizon. As they approach the white mass, they discover that the sea is covered in what?",
    "questionId": "ed18a87e595fc10e1cd611e88996e315",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Caspian",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Caspian",
      "Eustace",
      "Edmund",
      "Reepicheep"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the novel The Voyage of the Dawn Treader, the sea eventually becomes too shallow for the ship to continue and it must turn back, but several members of the crew will continue in the landing boat, hoping to reach Aslans country. On Aslans orders, which of the following characters was made to stay with the Dawn Treader for its return voyage?",
    "questionId": "93ae5a6e80a1503eef214443eeed32f7",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Dobby",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Sleepy",
      "Winky",
      "Dizzy",
      "Dobby"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the name of the house-elf who warned Harry Potter of not going back to school?",
    "questionId": "d3464403ae42f545b8fdf10d266381c7",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Dobby, the house-elf, has been collecting Harry Potters letters to make it seem as though his friends had forgotten him.",
    "questionId": "b80bc3140d96f8ee5d6d27cd172bbf34",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the book Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets, Harry used the Hover Charm to destroy a pudding that Aunt Petunia had made for an important dinner party attended by Uncle Vernons potential client and the clients wife.",
    "questionId": "7aa8e90cebbd6efaf9f298e2d87b706e",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets, the car which Harry and Ron rode on to Hogwarts, when they werent able to board on Hogwarts Express, crashed into the Whomping Willow.",
    "questionId": "18ef29b1ac6e1fa485a85d181d21f7f1",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Gilderoy Lockhart",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Remus Lupin",
      "Gilderoy Lockhart",
      "Dolores Umbridge",
      "Professor Quirrel"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What was the name of Harrys new Defense Against the Dark Arts teacher in the book Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets?",
    "questionId": "0e3b4d0f3050993add6dc64bffe0c1e6",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Being the last to go to the barrier between platform 9 and 10 at Kings Cross Station, Harry Potter and Ron were not able to get to platform nine and three-quarters.",
    "questionId": "711b0cd88efaf5f7e2b287280840be89",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Parseltongue",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Parsel Language",
      "Basilisks",
      "Snakish",
      "Parseltongue"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What do you call the fictional language of snakes, according to J. K. Rowlings second book in the Harry Potter series?",
    "questionId": "94c402b7b5938965da72d948e9c76ca1",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Lucius Malfoy put it in Ginnys cauldron.",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "She saw it lying on the floor and took it.",
      "She found it in her trunk.",
      "Lucius Malfoy put it in Ginnys cauldron.",
      "She found it in the girls bathroom at Hogwarts"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "How did Riddles Magical Diary go into Ginnys hand in the book Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets?",
    "questionId": "9d360eb8b1b5d5d8be9a2e74c1f52098",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets, Harry Potter destroyed Riddles Diary with one of the Basilisks poisonous fangs.",
    "questionId": "0dcf989271f4d461e7debc5a8bdf3e90",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Godric Gryffindor",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Salazar Slytherin",
      "Godric Gryffindor",
      "Helga Hufflepuff",
      "Rowena Ravenclaw"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Harry Potter draws a sword from the Sorting Hat during his duel with Tom Riddle and the Basilisk in the Chamber of Secrets. The sword belongs to which of the four founders of Hogwarts houses?",
    "questionId": "b740602ff84a2e6cc5bc009ad2182bdb",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "a sock",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "a sock",
      "a hat",
      "a pair of footwear",
      "a new shirt"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What sort of clothing freed Dobby, the house-elf, from the Malfoys according to the second Harry Potter book?",
    "questionId": "3f74c7476f9057f851967f15a9c0da9e",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Return to Narnia",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Return of the King",
      "Aslans Return",
      "Return of Prince Caspian",
      "Return to Narnia"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "C.S. Lewis titled his book, Prince Caspian, after the main character, but kept one of his working titles as a subtitle. What is the subtitle of this book?",
    "questionId": "ec779346287279776472cb6111d7d796",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "A hag and a werewolf",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "A vampire and an ogre",
      "A werewolf and an ogre",
      "A hag and a werewolf",
      "A hag and a vampire"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the novel Prince Caspian, what two creatures did the dwarf Nikabrik bring into Prince Caspians counsel in an attempt to convince him to use dark magic against King Miraz?",
    "questionId": "9488c2f63724ca96e6657b64979ff80e",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Lucy",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Lucy",
      "Susan",
      "Peter",
      "Edmund"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which of the Pevensie children first sees Aslan as they journey with the dwarf Trumpkin in the book Prince Caspian?",
    "questionId": "62bfe54c5c5dabe6ebc42359bd43b957",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Aslan stops the battle before anyone is killed.",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Miraz is betrayed and killed by his own noblemen.",
      "Aslan stops the battle before anyone is killed.",
      "Peter is wounded when Miraz puts his full weight into his shield.",
      "King Miraz stumbles and falls flat on his face."
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "During the battle between King Miraz and Peter depicted in the book Prince Caspian, which of the following does not happen?",
    "questionId": "6ae9c1c2dfc1f3df3d820144182274a1",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Reepicheep",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Peepicheek",
      "Cheekipeep",
      "Reepicheep",
      "Mickey"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the book Prince Caspian, what is the name of the Captain of the Mice, whom Aslan rewards with a new tail for the loyalty of his troops?",
    "questionId": "182265a638a43a205b12fd4a0abccbd8",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Both of these",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Miraz has recently had a son who he wishes to appoint as his heir.",
      "Neither of these",
      "Caspian is the rightful king of Narnia.",
      "Both of these"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "For what reason does King Miraz seek to kill Prince Caspian in the self-titled book?",
    "questionId": "89e0f58488c0ddfb147ae349bd57a3f9",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Before leaving Narnia in the novel Prince Caspian, Aslan informs Peter and Edmund that neither of them will be returning to Narnia.",
    "questionId": "ed1068ed0cc5d48151b51fd6a41c2ac1",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "A giant and a centaur",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "A bear and a squirrel",
      "A dwarf and a giant",
      "A giant and a centaur",
      "A mouse and a dwarf"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What two creatures accompany Edmund as he delivers Peters challenge to King Miraz in the book Prince Caspian?",
    "questionId": "69666855d513f90ba29edb71ec051d03",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "His old nurse and his tutor, Cornelius",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "His old nurse and his tutor, Cornelius",
      "High King Peter and King Edmund",
      "The magician Cornelius and the lion, Aslan",
      "His aunt, the queen and the dwarf Rikabrik"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the novel Prince Caspian, which two people are responsible for Prince Caspians great interest in Old Narnia?",
    "questionId": "7928757fbda1c897f689af0ef44a3b0d",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "The Tellmarines, featured in the novel Prince Caspian, are descendants of pirates that entered the land of Tellmar through a cave on an island.",
    "questionId": "105d35c51f28da96232cd99902b518ae",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Eagle",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Snake",
      "Bear",
      "Eagle",
      "Elephant"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is Ravenclaws symbol in the Harry Potter series?",
    "questionId": "aa5c415efa8abb629538b7b21927a4d9",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Hufflepuff",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Ravenclaw",
      "Hufflepuff",
      "Gryffindor",
      "Slytherin"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In which house is Susan Bones, one of the characters in the Harry Potter series?",
    "questionId": "251edad0a467df2092736f370ee8eb57",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "false",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Remus Lupin is related to Sirius Black.",
    "questionId": "33f72d35be49a9da65c6df2a7f8bbbe9",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Percy",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Percy",
      "Charlie",
      "Bill",
      "unknown by exact text"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Who owned Scabbers before Ron Weasley?",
    "questionId": "505cf79da0b8bb822986a0e92581dbc2",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Ginny died in Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets.",
    "questionId": "1b36ff6be4c834bcc7636518771d57a4",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the Harry Potter series, Rons uncle Billius saw a grim and died 25 hours later.",
    "questionId": "3b783e4e1f066ce4bc1f4b380fc7f261",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "false",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Harry Potter has a tattoo on his chest.",
    "questionId": "c8081fe9b33496d9fd6c7c2fafd264c6",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Malfoy",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Luna",
      "Cho",
      "Malfoy",
      "Anthony"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which of these Harry Potter characters is not a member of the D.A.?",
    "questionId": "ed79cc0b9eb557bd1255d6d83a9d95ba",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Death Eaters",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Death Munchers",
      "Death Eaters",
      "Death Masters",
      "Death Bugs"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What are Voldemorts followers called in the Harry Potter series?",
    "questionId": "9ff0fe5943a241b6017830c56fdc21a3",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Hermiones cats name is Crookshanks.",
    "questionId": "39b3c6c2ebfc39adc4c8bbce7c1a24fb",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Dark Master",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Dark Master",
      "Dark Lord",
      "You-Know-Who",
      "He-Who-Must-Not-Be-Named"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which of the following is not a name for Voldemort, the chief antagonist of the Harry Potter series?",
    "questionId": "55361c96dc3b0a8196c88dc2e87936ea",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Xenophilius",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Xewartqwe",
      "Piilotorpho",
      "Xenophilius",
      "Lenopillius"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the name of Luna Lovegoods father in the Harry Potter books?",
    "questionId": "f14658881c7e9d58a5a2b792332d7446",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Professor Snape is the Potions Master in Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince.",
    "questionId": "4612769199fa7084db3a00388159f7e4",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "true",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Grindelwald was defeated by Dumbledore in the Harry Potter series.",
    "questionId": "3e38e3fda3b476a19c6abab17225f223",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Harry Potter marries Hermione.",
    "questionId": "a653ed3c0dc1e3594f65ac5c20da1924",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "false",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Voldemort has a rat named Nagini.",
    "questionId": "2ce6f045f009ad9456db4df7ac3ceaf7",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the Disney movie, The Beauty and the Beast, all of the residents of the Beasts castle were mystical creatures.",
    "questionId": "feccfa90f1a83c26955b1dd5d1a95a4c",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Emma Watson plays Hermione Granger in the Harry Potter film series.",
    "questionId": "d9ea850ee1c6e99ce1151553ff0f108a",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Rupert Grint",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Rupert Grint",
      "Rupert Grant",
      "Hugh Mitchell",
      "Richard Harris"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What English actor portrays Harry Potters best friend, Ron Weasley?",
    "questionId": "bd08a3d070256257bb469cc6793d4fcc",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Nearly Headless Nick",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "The Fat Friar",
      "Nearly Headless Nick",
      "Peeves The Poltergeist",
      "The Bloody Baron"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What Gryffindor House ghost does John Cleese play in the Harry Potter film series?",
    "questionId": "62d1f2076aec285adbda289265a5a833",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Rubeus Hagrid",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Aberforth Dumbledore",
      "Rubeus Hagrid",
      "Bill Weasley",
      "Sirius Black"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What member of the Order of the Phoenix is portrayed by actor Robbie Coltrane?",
    "questionId": "8f061345214c3a7a97c4e0987a910521",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Richard Harris",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Richard Martin",
      "Robbie Coltrane",
      "Richard Harris",
      "Richard Griffiths"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Name the first actor who played Professor Dumbledore in the Harry Potter film series.",
    "questionId": "9e8ef45724cdd83cabcd1210f657d13c",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Tom Felton",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Tom Felton",
      "Alan Rickman",
      "Matthew Lewis",
      "David Bradley"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Who portrays Draco Malfoy, one of the antagonists in the Harry Potter series?",
    "questionId": "67c80401dcf35fe94e49661f07eb6fc5",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Jason Isaacs - Lord Voldemort",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Emma Thompson - Sybill Trelawney",
      "Helena Bonham Carter - Bellatrix Lestrange",
      "Alan Rickman - Severus Snape",
      "Jason Isaacs - Lord Voldemort"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What actor is not correctly paired with the character they played in the Harry Potter films?",
    "questionId": "6548031dfaa3939e18f9c9e599382b95",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Felix Felicis",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Everlasting Elixirs",
      "Emerald Green Potion",
      "Confusing Concoction",
      "Felix Felicis"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which potion in the Harry Potter series increases the luck of the drinker?",
    "questionId": "942746a9efe5d6026ae19990f20c4561",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Sleeping Draught",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Sleeping Draught",
      "Draught of Peace",
      "Forgetfulness Potion",
      "Calming Draught"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "This potion from the Harry Potter books induces a deep dreamless sleep in the drinker.",
    "questionId": "d3a951078be6a603212728b1ec2fcd8e",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Essence of Dittany",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Essence of Dittany",
      "Mandrake Restorative Draught",
      "Skele-Gro",
      "Amortentia"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What potion in the Harry Potter series helps stop bleeding and heal wounds?",
    "questionId": "e008799a5ce6e4e103fd82d3451b7cd8",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Wolfsbane Potion",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Essence of Murtlap",
      "Wolfsbane Potion",
      "Beautification Potion",
      "Elixir of Life"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What potion relieves the symptoms of lycanthropy in the Harry Potter series?",
    "questionId": "a89f262f2cd0708ad52483a6e16af068",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Veritaserum",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Memory Potion",
      "Veritaserum",
      "Babbling Beverage",
      "Polyjuice Potion"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "This potion is described by J.K. Rowling as so powerful that three drops would have you spilling your innermost secrets for the entire class to hear.",
    "questionId": "5a978c7faad71d12228f3844d7dadc30",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Love Potion",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Wit-Sharpening Potion",
      "Elixir to Induce Euphoria",
      "Love Potion",
      "Pepperup Potion"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the Harry Potter books, this potion causes the drinker to become infatuated or obsessed with the one who gave it to them.",
    "questionId": "4ceb3876d967e2126d8e290ef2f628b9",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Polyjuice Potion",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Befuddlement Draught",
      "Swelling Solution",
      "Skele-Gro",
      "Polyjuice Potion"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "This potion, mentioned in the Harry Potter books, allows the drinker to assume the appearance of another person.",
    "questionId": "e09313ae25ee8fcfa10b8d376a0b76ea",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Pepperup Potion",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Calming Draught",
      "Shrinking Solution",
      "Pepperup Potion",
      "Hiccoughing Solution"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What potion is used to help treat colds in the Harry Potter books?",
    "questionId": "9adeb33651d192934ee382091b68fa9c",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Elixir of Life",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Strengthening Solution",
      "Mandrake Restorative Draft",
      "Draught of Living Death",
      "Elixir of Life"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which potion, introduced in Harry Potter and the Philosophers Stone, lengthens the lifespan of the drinker as long as they keep drinking it?",
    "questionId": "216bf45a80e45b0943993b1a5980a81e",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Aging Potion",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Aging Potion",
      "Confusing Concoction",
      "Swelling Solution",
      "Befuddlement Draught"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What potion from the Harry Potter books causes the drinker to become older?",
    "questionId": "a40097910438d0381a2768133d11b999",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "unknown by exact text",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Yaxley",
      "Bellatrix",
      "unknown by exact text",
      "Rookwood"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which Death Eater killed Fred Weasley in Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows?",
    "questionId": "67e5786d37d99cbdb73e0cb8b79a8d95",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Fictional character Severus Snape was a Death Eater when he died.",
    "questionId": "e27b5f93f2136f16253cea6dbdbb5ba5",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Fenrir Greyback",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Fenrir Greyback",
      "Dolohov",
      "Rookwood",
      "Yaxley"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which Death Eater bit Lupin?",
    "questionId": "91f7b1f5092a3e8f4aca2d591a937a8f",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Fictional character Augustus Rookwood worked in the Department of Mysteries.",
    "questionId": "a09bbfa32507826b9b5dc01df16e3a33",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "spider",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "spider",
      "spyglass",
      "spyer",
      "spurr"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the answer to the riddle the sphinx gives to Harry Potter in the maze for the third task of of the Triwizard Tournament?",
    "questionId": "2cb8d0ec1e8e1fbb4d0d888a581d8d8b",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Harry Potter",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Viktor Krum",
      "Fleur Delacour",
      "Harry Potter",
      "Cedric Diggory"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the name of the fourth champion of the fictional Triwizard Tournament?",
    "questionId": "c91c567ea2591e6a24160faa91cf378f",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Flesh, Blood, and Bone",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "The Death Eaters",
      "Prior Incantatem",
      "The Third Task",
      "Flesh, Blood, and Bone"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the name of the chapter in Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire in which Cedric Diggory dies?",
    "questionId": "ed577c026bde63da154d9d3218ba3bd2",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "false",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Harry Potter fights a dementor in the maze in the third task of the Triwizard Tournament.",
    "questionId": "5a80651d0ce7e395dfea3150b98b1b27",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Chinese Fireball",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Swedish Shortsnout",
      "Chinese Fireball",
      "Welsh Green",
      "Hungarian Horntail"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the name of the dragon Viktor Krum has to fight for the first task of the Triwizard Tournament?",
    "questionId": "27853c2ed1394a0445381aa7234c719c",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "eats gillyweed",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "eats gillyweed",
      "uses breathing equipment",
      "uses bubblehead charm",
      "transforms into a shark"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What does Harry Potter do to be able to breathe underwater for the second task of the Triwizard Tournament?",
    "questionId": "78bf4dd4eb5ffe5d24bfa02a80540932",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "prefects bathroom",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "prefects bathroom",
      "girls bathroom",
      "teachers bathroom",
      "boys bathroom"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Where is Harry Potter when he finds out what the second task of the Triwizard Tournament is about?",
    "questionId": "a1980cee473e11d143c0800f6e58f6e6",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Harry Potter wins 10,000 galleons for winning the Triwizard Tournament.",
    "questionId": "f8036adc9f493798b1f3a2c20e6f2068",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "1908",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "1919",
      "1908",
      "1925",
      "1955"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In what year was the novel Anne of Green Gables published?",
    "questionId": "3e958ff0512de0cecfa627fe5b289fb1",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Nova Scotia",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "New Brunswick",
      "Maine",
      "Nova Scotia",
      "Newfoundland"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What was the location of the orphanage from which Anne was adopted in the book Anne of Green Gables?",
    "questionId": "712b6d1c81e1de8b66cb9e4bfcc31e24",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Brother and Sister",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Father and Daughter",
      "Husband and Wife",
      "Brother and Sister",
      "They were cousins"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What was the relationship between Matthew and Marilla, the couple who adopted Anne in Lucy Montgomerys book?",
    "questionId": "1578c188b9921b0b6973c1ea440c979a",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "8",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "5",
      "8",
      "3",
      "10"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "How many books are there in the L. M. Montgomery Anne series?",
    "questionId": "11fa0efa878b6302037ebdd6066e8b21",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "She mistook a bottle of currant wine for the raspberry cordial she was supposed to serve for tea and got drunk.",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "She mistook a bottle of currant wine for the raspberry cordial she was supposed to serve for tea and got drunk.",
      "She forgot to replace the cheesecloth cover on the pudding sauce and a mouse drowned in it.",
      "She bought hair dye from a peddler and instead of the desired black, it turned her hair green.",
      "She broke her slate over a schoolmates head when he teasingly called her carrots."
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the book Anne of Green Gables Anne gets herself into many predicaments.  Which of the following is NOT one of them?",
    "questionId": "6c97661b9194653af282436b00f6c368",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Prince Edward Island",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "None of these",
      "Prince Edward Island",
      "New Brunswick",
      "Nova Scotia"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In what Canadian province do Marilla and Matthew Cuthbert live in the book Anne of Green Gables?",
    "questionId": "020e00ac7e3df7daf65230a4a6614b19",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Avonlea",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Carmody",
      "Cavendish",
      "Avonlea",
      "White Sands"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the name of the fictional town in which the story of Anne of Green Gables unfolds?",
    "questionId": "e4a1a2e89d23b78d1be50d8405ce1856",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Shirley",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Pye",
      "Blythe",
      "Shirley",
      "Cuthbert"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which of the following is Annes surname in the book Anne of Green Gables?",
    "questionId": "93c0b04fd256815525a1c3c05812736a",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Bosom friends",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Two peas in a pod",
      "Bosom friends",
      "Truer than blue",
      "Friends til the end"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Diana Barry is Annes best friend in the book Anne of Green Gables. How did Anne describe their friendship?",
    "questionId": "6486e94013f96d32d21d800b056f42c0",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "1964",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "1960",
      "1964",
      "1970",
      "1972"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "When was Anne of Green Gables - The Musical performed for the first time?",
    "questionId": "76ec6e19711edc93e5deb5ad1f527660",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "They dont have puffed sleeves.",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "They dont have flounces.",
      "They dont have petticoats.",
      "They dont have puffed sleeves.",
      "They dont have any lace trimming."
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Early in the story of Anne of Green Gables, Marilla proudly presents Anne with three new dresses which she has made to replace the shabby, orphanage issued clothes but is very annoyed when it becomes obvious that Anne doesnt like them. Why doesnt Anne like them?",
    "questionId": "7e2f693a108d1140e03ba0c5ef5b27a2",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The Confederation Center of the Arts",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "The Green Gables Theater of the Arts",
      "The Cradle of Confederation Theater",
      "The Centennial Theater of the Arts",
      "The Confederation Center of the Arts"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the name of the theater in which Anne of Green Gables - The Musical plays every summer?",
    "questionId": "70a82663bb91fc7c61be1f4e798589ab",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Colleen Dewhurst",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Colleen Dewhurst",
      "Ellen Burstyn",
      "Patricia Hamilton",
      "Rosemary Radcliff"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "This Emmy Award-winning actress played Marilla in the 1985 television production of Anne of Green Gables, written and directed by Kevin Sullivan.",
    "questionId": "61753d873bf33160e23b006b04690f80",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "All of these",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "All of these",
      "Bossy",
      "Prying",
      "Opinionated"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What adjective best describes the character of Mrs. Rachel Lynde from the book Anne of Green Gables?",
    "questionId": "fa06b25c9fbb306082a30e3376f780de",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "At the end of the novel Anne of Green Gables, Matthew Cuthbert dies from complications related to pneumonia.",
    "questionId": "1fd998e0a842d7a01438ca33a2aa9fc7",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "$25.00",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "$2.50",
      "$250.00",
      "$25.00",
      "$25.50"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Sam had $3.00, Bob had $9.50, Joe had $5.25, and Jim had $7.25. How much is all of their money together worth?",
    "questionId": "af73971af96bd3bc799b22f675d54e7a",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "12",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "11",
      "9",
      "12",
      "6"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which one of these numbers does not fit in the sequence: 2 4 6 7 9 12 11?",
    "questionId": "c23b57502cd90a1201ac1a22d61a17bf",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "12.3",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "32.1",
      "3.21",
      "1.23",
      "12.3"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What do you get when you divide 123 by 10?",
    "questionId": "34f6f1699b8bcef1d063cb21af5eb35c",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "842",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "284",
      "824",
      "428",
      "842"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "There are three digits in this number. The first digit (of the hundreds) is 8. Divide it by two, that is your second digit, divide the result again by two, that is your third digit. What is the number?",
    "questionId": "b2ff81309dbbf0112b52a52bf7067a94",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "false",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "All these numbers fit and make sense in sequence: 1, 2, 3, 5, 7, 9.",
    "questionId": "7542a2b264f1da3c0b80329c973d38ee",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "76.5",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "74.5",
      "76.5",
      "76",
      "75"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "How much is 765 divided by 10?",
    "questionId": "240e9b3b25e7a323934973710bb8b238",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "20",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "3",
      "9",
      "15",
      "20"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which of the following numbers doesnt belong to the others: 3, 9, 15, 20?",
    "questionId": "e467fd094dd2d61d7f7abea17eb846a6",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "16",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "16",
      "32",
      "8",
      "4"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "A person owned 8 dogs and as many cats. What is the total amount of pets owned by that somebody?",
    "questionId": "b02a39b792754f6a0cb4cc4c404a0d6d",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The locket",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Hufflepuffs cup",
      "The locket",
      "None of these",
      "Nagini"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the first Horcrux found in Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows?",
    "questionId": "fdd63d19b5e3ea8718a731f8e0656e0b",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "false",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Harry Potter destroyed Tom Riddle's diary in the second book because he knew it was a horcrux.",
    "questionId": "7cb9fa0cda95fce5a816931fcb7a2dcb",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Basilisk Fangs",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Gryffindors sword",
      "Their Wands",
      "Nothing, Harry destroyed it.",
      "Basilisk Fangs"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What did Ron and Hermione use to destroy Hufflepuffs cup?",
    "questionId": "d96f4801cf00cb6cba1ebe223caa7069",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "One of the Horcruxes in the Harry Potter books is Ravenclaws cup.",
    "questionId": "a594a74748bac15e8674268f3dc3bfc0",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "7",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "10",
      "7",
      "2",
      "5"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "How many Horcruxes did Tom Riddle make?",
    "questionId": "1020c7c422f3950fac3e7a46e7b8fea6",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "According to the Harry Potter series of books, any object can be a Horcrux.",
    "questionId": "ba136053aadbf5668f245729d7e32fa7",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "false",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "If one of Voldemort's horcruxes is destroyed, he will instantly know.",
    "questionId": "8214f37ad91b17a311378102c05a667b",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Nagini, one of Voldemorts Horcruxes, is a snake.",
    "questionId": "24d491f9b7f5ddb90613de7e74bd4306",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "13",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "13",
      "55",
      "22",
      "7"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "How old was Charlotte, the protagonist of The True Confessions of Charlotte Doyle, when she took the trip from England to her home on Rhode Island?",
    "questionId": "f0d710117b168b2d20cff215a2674f87",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The Seahawk",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "The Seahawk",
      "The Seacraft",
      "The Doyle Express",
      "The Charlotte Doyle"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What was the name of the ship that Charlotte boarded in the book The True Confessions of Charlotte Doyle?",
    "questionId": "7c9025e498f4e499152db3d28eaac0b7",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the book The True Confessions of Charlotte Doyle, the crew wanted to get revenge on the Captain.",
    "questionId": "e00ef1c90557a126f2258d4eb7ecb8c6",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Charlotte was the only female on the ship in the book The True Confessions of Charlotte Doyle.",
    "questionId": "d184984752adce25c437d26cb90e71f8",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In The True Confessions of Charlotte Doyle, the men from the crew plan to kill Charlotte because she supported the Captain.",
    "questionId": "71bd93b039cd747a13cd7abe55b0c5fd",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Zachariah, a character from the book The True Confessions of Charlotte Doyle, is brutally beaten to death by the Captain and Mr. Hollybrass.",
    "questionId": "7d2650427d416dcca8f152cad8f9e324",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Charlotte",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Charlotte",
      "The ships ghost",
      "Himself",
      "Zachariah"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Who does the Captain blame for the murder of Mr. Hollybrass in the book The True Confessions of Charlotte Doyle?",
    "questionId": "2df634419368bf793875b6e52926ae57",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "hanging",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "hanging",
      "a week in the brig",
      "getting your hands cut off",
      "getting locked in a room with the ships ghost"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "According to the book The True Confessions of Charlotte Doyle, what is the penalty for murder of a ships First Mate?",
    "questionId": "5571fb1e6010eb59e9ded3c0ef919cbd",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "The Captain in the book The True Confessions of Charlotte Doyle dies.",
    "questionId": "2376a974e5c20845696732d6834dd37d",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Her tongue/voice",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Her soul",
      "Her heart",
      "Her tongue/voice",
      "Her necklace"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What does the Sea Witch want from the Little Mermaid in exchange for the magic potion in Andersens fairy tale The Little Mermaid?",
    "questionId": "98e69a582ed7c11770d7808d6b84cf09",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Someone is dying",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Someone is dying",
      "God is crying",
      "Someone is born",
      "An angel is coming to earth from Heaven"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the meaning of a falling star according to the late grandmother in Andersens The Little Match Girl?",
    "questionId": "d4484a1efd7f637299d7caad09b1026f",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "They put it in the Royal Museum",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "They put it in the Royal Museum",
      "They split it and eat it",
      "An anger takes it to Heaven",
      "A dove eats it"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What happens to the pea after the prince marries the princess in the fairy tale The Princess and the Pea?",
    "questionId": "3cf0a7c9dbad2014a2bc0bcf7b723eb0",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Speak",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Smile",
      "Cut her hair",
      "Go out in the sunlight",
      "Speak"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is Elisa forbidden to do until she finishes knitting the eleven nettle shirts in Hans Christian Andersens fairy tale The Wild Swans?",
    "questionId": "e4d422cb1015e19a0181f154f7197fe2",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Eternity",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Forgiveness",
      "Eternity",
      "Love",
      "Purity"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the word that Kai has to spell using pieces of ice in order to regain his freedom in Andersens fairy tale The Snow Queen?",
    "questionId": "f15bba509e0ec5af97bc8901245ffd8a",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Maya",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Bella",
      "Rosalind",
      "Maya",
      "Lily"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What new name is Thumbelina given at the end of the fairy tale Thumbelina?",
    "questionId": "f93d1993c731fb99ea2b15670c0a7739",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Cat and hen",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Cat and dog",
      "Cat and hen",
      "Hen and dog",
      "Geese"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What animals mock the little duck in Hans Christian Andersens fairy tale The Ugly Duckling?",
    "questionId": "ee4215558d68cae848856a992c11f56a",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Stupid people",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Liars",
      "Stupid people",
      "Criminals",
      "All of these"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What kind of people are unable to see the clothes of the emperor according to the frauds in the fairy tale The Emperors New Clothes?",
    "questionId": "9a8f4467a6c85b965234ebff56700153",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "They are both standing on one leg",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "They are dressed in white",
      "They are both standing on one leg",
      "They love listening to the gramophone",
      "They are both very sad"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "According to The Steadfast Tin Soldier, what do the tin soldier and the paper ballerina have in common that makes the soldier fall in love?",
    "questionId": "9ed8360491c599aa17df7d7b126448ad",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "He is moved by the song of the bird",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "God forces him to go away",
      "He is moved by the song of the bird",
      "He takes the Emperors nightingale in exchange for his life",
      "He gets scared from a Chinese mask"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Why does Death decide to spare the Chinese Emperors life in the fairy tale The Nightingale by Hans Christian Andersen?",
    "questionId": "37054dc9d0d1e79c8d47c81c8ea946f8",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "54",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "54",
      "50",
      "52",
      "53"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "How many people died in the fictional Battle of Hogwarts?",
    "questionId": "59fa7281b482f693c358240c11152ded",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "28",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "25",
      "26",
      "29",
      "28"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "How many people are in the fictional student organisation known as Dumbledores Army?",
    "questionId": "8da5a4dffd4f4f38d962642ddd3bbf28",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "6",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "3",
      "5",
      "4",
      "6"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "How many siblings does Ron Weasley have?",
    "questionId": "d4edbd10b1fdbff1ae2198fdb210650e",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "4",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "5",
      "1",
      "4",
      "3"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "How many people were selected for the Triwizard Tournament in Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire?",
    "questionId": "41f0b37b392c900b310194341f98b4a8",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "10",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "15",
      "9",
      "10",
      "8"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "How many O.W.L.s did Hermione Granger get in the Harry Potter books?",
    "questionId": "d8c917b196f4fe22805677b2720bc795",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "50",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "55",
      "45",
      "40",
      "50"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "How many dementors attacked Harry and Hermione in the end of Book 3 of the Harry Potter series?",
    "questionId": "aa4780190b0841631d898481abf0a986",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "7",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "9",
      "8",
      "6",
      "7"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "How many floors are in the fictional Hogwarts school?(excluding the dungeons)",
    "questionId": "452cd29010b0420ea235b29f62f1fd7f",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "December 25th",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "December 25th",
      "November 25th",
      "October 25th",
      "January 25th"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "On what day did Harry Potter discover the Mirror of Erised?",
    "questionId": "dc8fb46fed4d562fc4599bae4ca08f81",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "7th",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "5th",
      "7th",
      "6th",
      "3rd"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "On what floor of the fictional Hogwarts school do you find the Room of Requirement?",
    "questionId": "dea40f29acd8ffe0cc8574fbd0a020e3",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "3",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "2",
      "3",
      "4",
      "1"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "How many people died in the book Harry Potter and the Sorcerers Stone?",
    "questionId": "c417ee8ee41506455a39909a59987874",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "What the?",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Whats this doing here?",
      "Ouch!",
      "Hush up Hedwig",
      "What the?"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is Harrys first line in the book Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows?",
    "questionId": "4103f95c4107a9e922a2f8b0cb497e06",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Fictional character Rita Skeeter wrote a book titled Albus Dumbledore, His Life and Lies.",
    "questionId": "d9fd4fcbcf9cc9a2fd1f6ca8c056632d",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "false",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Albus Dumbledore's sister was named Areida.",
    "questionId": "a70383913f91d6bd872d082435a6f9de",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Kingsley Shacklebolt",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Fred Weasley",
      "Arthur Weasley",
      "Kingsley Shacklebolt",
      "Bill Weasley"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Who does Hermione Granger fly with when leaving Privet Drive?",
    "questionId": "529c7e65cdc5a918762206b3d137e5f2",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Muffliato",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Suctesemptra",
      "Muffliato",
      "Demuestio",
      "Fiendfyre"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What spell does Hermione not approve of according to the book Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows?",
    "questionId": "1aca06fbff14ef06d828aa69e0a399a7",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows, Ron leaves the group when they are in the forest of Dean.",
    "questionId": "e7ce93f06bdf9ddc489dd3b9d190fe6c",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Ron",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Ron",
      "Harry",
      "Hermione",
      "Ginny"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What character first discovered that the name Voldemort was cursed?",
    "questionId": "2d083a2fd97b642a22651b1101c17b51",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "It is mentioned in Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows that Bill had a real knack for guessing the passwords for the radio.",
    "questionId": "f371e892e927837e1fce5b5659a50bfd",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "A goblin",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Dragomir",
      "He doesnt use unforgivable curses.",
      "A goblin",
      "Travers"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Who does Harry first use the Imperius curse on in Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows?",
    "questionId": "a3d02670babd8860f577f4a9298dfc56",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "According to the Harry Potter books, Fleur Delacours middle name is Clemence.",
    "questionId": "b4c81cda1b49ffdc8fe5902b8e3ff7df",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Gemino",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Gemino",
      "Duplique",
      "Multiplico",
      "Magrante"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the name of the spell that multiplies objects in the Harry Potter books?",
    "questionId": "487a41f8d5f467846847231b200178fe",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Mulciber and Avery",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Mulciber and Avery",
      "Macnair and Lucius",
      "James and Sirius",
      "Lucius and Lestrange"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the chapter of Harry Potter and the Deadly Hallows, titled The Princes Tale, Lily states that these two boys idea of humor is, just evil.",
    "questionId": "9b3b1f9a884a7b367d9b70e35d6c5d7a",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "McGonagall",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Hermione",
      "McGonagall",
      "Ginny",
      "Ron"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What characters screams at the end of Harry Potter and the Deadly Hallows on learning of Harrys apparent death.",
    "questionId": "e013b1f63b02f7a0449ee5c6a46c5da9",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "true",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Voldemort tells Neville that he has spirit and bravery in the last book of the Harry Potter series.",
    "questionId": "80a237e1386a64fc1977fafab20c29f1",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "January 29, 1959",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "May 25, 1944",
      "January 29, 1959",
      "August 1, 1966",
      "February 14, 1951"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Sleeping Beauty was the last fairy tale produced by Walt Disney.  When was it released?",
    "questionId": "e39f1d98b3697309415970ceae2918ca",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Sleeping Beautys musical score and songs were inspired by Pyotr Ilyich Tchaikovskys Sleeping Beauty ballet.",
    "questionId": "d90b272ba13b7eaf7afe1ae070810d66",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The goddess of the dawn",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "The goddess of the dawn",
      "The goddess of the moon",
      "The goddess of the forests",
      "The goddess of the clouds"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the Disney movie Sleeping Beauty, Princess Aurora is born to King Stefan and Queen Leah and they name her Aurora after what Roman goddess?",
    "questionId": "770b56e9611f5773c45a9e101f4c8ee4",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "She was not invited to the christening.",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "She was in line to inherit the kingdom before Aurora was born.",
      "She is in love with the king.",
      "She hates the queen, her sister.",
      "She was not invited to the christening."
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the popular Disney animated film Maleficent curses baby Aurora: she will die when she pricks her finger on a spinning wheels spindle.  Why does Maleficent arrive and curse the child?",
    "questionId": "868d0e2ed30cf33b4ef44668c5862aaa",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "She weakens the curse so Aurora will only fall into a deep sleep.",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "She makes Aurora able to live for 500 years.",
      "She weakens the curse so Aurora will only fall into a deep sleep.",
      "She curses Maleficent with death.",
      "She makes a valiant prince fall in love with Aurora."
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the gift of the third fairy in the Disney movie Sleeping Beauty?",
    "questionId": "08b68b26e35925336c217cb1ab964e84",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "commands all spinning wheels be destroyed",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "locks Aurora in a tower",
      "tries to have another witch remove the curse",
      "commands all spinning wheels be destroyed",
      "kills Maleficent"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "The three fairies in the animated film Sleeping Beauty decide to conceal Aurora in a cabin in the woods until her 16th birthday passes, but before the fairies take Aurora to the woods, what does the King do to stop the curse?",
    "questionId": "06eb5fe828e9f08cba9bba33b2036989",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Briar Rose",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Dahlia",
      "Topaz",
      "Briar Rose",
      "Jasmine"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What do the fairies rename Aurora in the Disney movie Sleeping Beauty?",
    "questionId": "e449fb2ba4c75f22e7720357e7292971",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "She sends out her raven Diablo to find Aurora.",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "She consults her crystal ball for Aurora.",
      "She sends out her raven Diablo to find Aurora.",
      "She disguises herself as a peasant and searches for Aurora.",
      "She puts the prince under a spell and sends him to search for Aurora."
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the animated movie Sleeping Beauty, just prior to Auroras 16th birthday, Maleficent is furious that she and her evil henchmen still cannot find Aurora. What does Maleficent do?",
    "questionId": "b653719a0bbdf881c8a2013c22dc5271",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "A cake and a gown",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "A gown and a cape",
      "A cake and a gown",
      "A cake and a quilt",
      "A pie and a gown"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the movie Sleeping Beauty, on Auroras 16th birthday, the fairies decide to make two presents, but their attempts fail and they use their wands, thus giving away their location. What two items were the fairies making for Aurora?",
    "questionId": "ca2d2a089c051eb1b605838bca5bcc09",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the Disney movie Sleeping Beauty, when Aurora returns to the cabin, the fairies tell her who she really is and take her to the castle to see her parents.",
    "questionId": "5f4664e02d959d620418fc5cb472662b",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The fairies",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "The queen",
      "The king",
      "The fairies",
      "The prince"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the movie Sleeping Beauty, back at home in the castle, Aurora finds a spinning wheel in the castles tower, pricks her finger on the spindle and falls into a deep sleep. Who finds Aurora?",
    "questionId": "e80c0e97fff3526f0e6616a63b68210a",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the Disney movie Sleeping Beauty, once Aurora falls into her deep sleep, the fairies freeze time until the spell is broken.",
    "questionId": "f8a2b93636027f3138a45691f9d812a4",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The Forbidden Mountain",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "The Lair",
      "The Den of Thorns",
      "The Forbidden Mountain",
      "The Dark Palace"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the Disney film Sleeping Beauty, the fairies find out that Prince Phillip is the man Aurora loves and the only one who can break the spell, but Maleficents henchmen capture him and take him to Maleficents castle. What is the castle called?",
    "questionId": "64240e8588dc0608e35d418beea8fbb2",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "A sword and a shield",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "A robe and sword",
      "A watch and a book",
      "A sword and a shield",
      "A rose and a robe"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the animated movie Sleeping Beauty, the fairies enter Maleficents castle and free the prince and give him these two magical objects.",
    "questionId": "d873a52ece54fab410e95950b833ed97",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Pink",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Pink",
      "Blue",
      "Purple",
      "Green"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the animated film Sleeping Beauty, Aurora and Prince Phillip dance a waltz and do not notice the fairies magically changing the color of Auroras ball gown.  As the book closes, Auroras gown turns this color and remains this color.",
    "questionId": "3dd6fb701e59e60a32492c84d77c2728",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "$478.22 million",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "$102.49 million",
      "$478.22 million",
      "$668.39 million",
      "$309.2 million"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Sleeping Beauty was re-released theatrically in 1970, 1971, 1986, 1993, 1995, and 2008. How much did it gross in theatres in the period 1959-2009, when adjusted for ticket price inflation?",
    "questionId": "4599b8fe9132b0c2b4ceb14c1e34090a",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "She couldnt bear to see anyone else play Hermione.",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "She joked that she stayed because she was in love with Rupert Grint.",
      "Her parents talked her into staying.",
      "She did it for the fans.",
      "She couldnt bear to see anyone else play Hermione."
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Why did actress Emma Watson, who plays Hermione in the Harry Potter series, keep her role in the sixth movie, Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince 2009, after initially deciding to quit?",
    "questionId": "bcd96b7314f07510504283505e2f453a",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Comic character",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Comic character",
      "Unique character",
      "Tragic character",
      "Ambiguous character"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "How did actor Jim Broadbent describe his character, Horace Slughorn, from the sixth Harry Potter movie, Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince 2009?",
    "questionId": "e5d5ed868091b5fd201f5464f0728e1b",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Naomi Watts",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Kate Winslet",
      "Meg Ryan",
      "Naomi Watts",
      "Melanie Griffith"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "This actress reportedly accepted the role of Narcissa Malfoy for the 2009 movie Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince, but her agent stated that the rumors were not true.",
    "questionId": "8a8dca4cadcf97fe0be8530770817c05",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Severus Snape",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Draco Malfoy",
      "Albus Dumbledore",
      "Severus Snape",
      "Sirius Black"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Who turns out to be the Half-Blood Prince in the sixth Harry Potter movie Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince?",
    "questionId": "e93c52f415e2f697610e68487615172c",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Padfoot",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Bagger",
      "Padfoot",
      "Mole",
      "Dazzler"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the nickname of Sirius Black, whose younger brother Regulus Black appears in a photograph owned by Horace Slughorn in the movie Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince 2009?",
    "questionId": "5aa095f1c60145263e2cd561bca22fb5",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Ginny Weasley",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Fleur Delacour",
      "Lavender Brown",
      "All of these",
      "Ginny Weasley"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "With whom does Harry Potter form a relationship in the 2009 movie Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince?",
    "questionId": "522e791e924c8156a095106250aecace",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Both the battle in the castle and Dumbledores funeral were not in the script.",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Dumbledores funeral was not in the script.",
      "Both the battle in the castle and Dumbledores funeral were not in the script.",
      "The climactic battle in the castle was not in the script.",
      "No changes were made."
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What are the differences between the original plot of the book and the script of 2009 movie Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince?",
    "questionId": "6b5137b6c4f2050d9ae8567b05183560",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "David Copperfield",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "David Copperfield",
      "Peter Pan",
      "Adolf Hitler",
      "Harry Potter"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What popular personality did actor Daniel Radcliffe portray in his debut movie?",
    "questionId": "4e2a6284b3b04e3bc3fe630ea2daaa3e",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "A fish",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "One of Noahs sons",
      "A lion",
      "Noah",
      "A fish"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What kind of character did actor Rupert Grint from the 2009 Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince depict in a play based on the story of Noahs Ark when he was little?",
    "questionId": "b0df51ef53e622282710879137b4a8fe",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Emma Watson",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Helena Bonham Carter",
      "Jessie Cave",
      "Bonnie Wright",
      "Emma Watson"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which of these cast members of the 2009 movie Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince was born in Paris, France?",
    "questionId": "df929077f193ef632c97442fef481a87",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Swallow",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Nightingale",
      "Sparrow",
      "Hummingbird",
      "Swallow"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What kind of bird is the character from Oscar Wildes fairy tale The Happy Prince?",
    "questionId": "944be6224a1c7b6fa6c0c1bd3c3284cd",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "It paints a white rose with its blood",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "It steals one",
      "It paints a white rose with its blood",
      "It travels trough many countries and dies from exhaustion",
      "It prays to God and He sends one"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "How does the nightingale from Oscar Wildes story The Nightingale and the Rose find a red rose for the poor student?",
    "questionId": "b7b5b4970d37b2030c4d48204a2d9f24",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Eternal winter sets in the garden",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "There is no more sunshine in the garden, only darkness",
      "The small pond dries up and the fish dies",
      "All the flowers wither and the birds die",
      "Eternal winter sets in the garden"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What happens to the beautiful garden of the giant when he builds a wall to keep children off in Oscar Wildes fairy tale The Selfish Giant?",
    "questionId": "50716cabc6b352dd0c7af78a0a76fd80",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Hes a gardener",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "He is a musician",
      "He is a miller",
      "Hes a gardener",
      "Hes a doctor"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What does Hans from Oscar Wildes fairy tale The Devoted Friend do for a living?",
    "questionId": "8769c2dce17a9004a8febd2c48668192",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "It gets wet",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "It is too lofty",
      "It dies",
      "It is faulty",
      "It gets wet"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Why does the rocket from Oscar Wildes story The Remarkable Rocket fail to ignite?",
    "questionId": "fe2cab234cca81d721533bb53ec1cce4",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "He has nightmares of where it came from",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "He doesnt want to be a king",
      "He has nightmares of where it came from",
      "All of these",
      "He finds it ugly"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Why does the shepherd from Oscar Wildes fairy tale The Young King refuse to wear the royal raiment?",
    "questionId": "0af8b0e401e80dc3a6e9be809748ba71",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "For the future, let those who come to play with me have no hearts.",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Its a shame Ive forgotten who I was, so let the people decide my fate.",
      "For the future, let those who come to play with me have no hearts.",
      "Little people will never know what its like being a princess.",
      "Justice shall reign one day when I sit on the throne."
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the last line of the Infanta from Oscar Wildes story The Birthday of the Infanta?",
    "questionId": "33fa39215c3ea9592c6ed8995034e550",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "His heart",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "His only child",
      "His hope",
      "His most valuable possession",
      "His heart"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What does the Soul want from the fisherman in Oscar Wildes fairy tale The Fisherman and his Soul?",
    "questionId": "3eea0c2a503d5095183b737cc3b6ae82",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "A beggar",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "A beggar",
      "An angel",
      "A witch",
      "A star"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Who is the mother of the Star-Child from Oscar Wildes fairy tale The Star-Child?",
    "questionId": "a60e337bcbdb669e44986bc7581d1556",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "A cross between a snake and a toad",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "A cross between a snake and a toad",
      "A flower",
      "Vapor",
      "A black dove"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the beautiful Star-Child transformed into in Oscar Wildes fairy tale The Star-Child?",
    "questionId": "41da6fffe015a5d36c0d59321f58ecff",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Harry Potter, Voldemort, and Dumbledore have connected wands.",
    "questionId": "a38be69f19b8745628069e4b82b5b4e0",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Voldemort",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Voldemort",
      "Rookwood",
      "Bellatrix",
      "Igor Karkaroff"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which of these fictional characters is the leader of the Death Eaters?",
    "questionId": "fc5e77d661dfaaa87e6d2862904a3517",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "John",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Michael",
      "John",
      "Robert",
      "James"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What was the first name of the animated 1980s hero Blackstar?",
    "questionId": "7d0ee97dfd54aca96bbb9f4ea57661a0",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "After falling in a black hole",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "After an impact with an asteroid",
      "Because of his co-pilots incompetence",
      "After a time rift",
      "After falling in a black hole"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "How did Blackstar from the animated series of the same name get stranded in the alien world?",
    "questionId": "01a2e82fcc4b9b4da0ba03d6f2f0e2e6",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "1981",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "1980",
      "1981",
      "1983",
      "1979"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In what year were the Blackstar animated series first broadcast on American television?",
    "questionId": "bb28b5d9291e383eab6c37d7224c94b9",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Dargo",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Burble",
      "Carpo",
      "Dargo",
      "Balkar"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the Blackstar animates series, which of these was not a name of the little people known as the Trobbits?",
    "questionId": "0264f7eaac6991f73b88db3d76a10e97",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "13",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "16",
      "13",
      "20",
      "10"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "How many episodes of the animated series Blackstar ran on American television?",
    "questionId": "7c41a069adc5ffc84c1546e9c7ef3b2b",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "A. A. Milne",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "William Horwood",
      "E. H. Shepard",
      "Kenneth Grahame",
      "A. A. Milne"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "The Wind in the Willows was published in 1908 without much notice. What famous author and playwright, best known for Winnie the Pooh, adapted part of the book for the stage in 1929, thus making the book famous?",
    "questionId": "661ea6694a4ebba4359f149cc5dfb686",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "spring cleaning",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "trying to sleep",
      "listening to Mr. Toad",
      "spring cleaning",
      "looking for food"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "At the beginning of the book The Wind in the Willows, what is Mole doing when he gets angry and goes above ground to the river?",
    "questionId": "97854ed2a9d35ed2166e73c699d1c368",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Mr. Toad",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Mole",
      "Mr. Toad",
      "Weasel",
      "Pan"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What character from The Wind in the Willows becomes easily obsessed with items, only to forget about them soon after acquiring them?",
    "questionId": "7db6945b23486075f8c984fad842cb01",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Kenneth Grahame",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "E. H. Shepard",
      "A. A. Milne",
      "Kenneth Grahame",
      "James Blish"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "The Wind in the Willows was first published in 1908. What Scottish-born writer and author of the story The Reluctant Dragon wrote this book?",
    "questionId": "12a4f0109fcc77c83e63208a298916ee",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Mole",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Otter",
      "Mr. Toad",
      "Mole",
      "Weasel"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What character from The Wind in the Willows gets lost in Wild Wood while looking for Badgers house?",
    "questionId": "aaf585a47ff351b7e3ea87866d7a7763",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Put him under house arrest",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Put him under house arrest",
      "Have him thrown in jail",
      "Burn his cars",
      "Make him live underground with Mole"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the novel The Wind in the Willows, Toad has crashed 6 cars, been put in the hospital for injuries 3 times, and has spent a great deal of money on fines. Toads friends decide to do this to save Toad since he has no sense when it comes to his obsessions.",
    "questionId": "572f4f97a0bd1fc1fe361c5b26bb084a",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The jailers daughter",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Toads cellmate",
      "The jailer",
      "Toads attorney",
      "The jailers daughter"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the novel The Wind in the Willows, while Mr. Toad is in jail, this person becomes fond of him and helps him escape.",
    "questionId": "fc98b6d288930420ae4705c1181130aa",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "A washerwoman",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "A police officer",
      "An attractive female",
      "The jailer",
      "A washerwoman"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In order to escape, Toad from The Wind in the Willows is dressed in disguise. What is he disguised as?",
    "questionId": "16df9e27b6cc26565208b4373527739c",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Money and stew",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Money and stew",
      "A ride back to Toad Hall",
      "Another disguise",
      "A place to spend the night"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the book The Wind in the Willows, shortly after his escape and still in disguise, Mr. Toad meets a bargewoman and tricks her into giving him a job. The bargewoman discovers Toads trick and throws him overboard. He steals her horse and sells it to a Gypsy for what?",
    "questionId": "c05c1d845eaaf93cafc1128408e3b6e7",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "It is the same car that Toad stole earlier",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "It is Toads car, and Badger is the driver",
      "It is Rats car, and Badger is the driver",
      "It is the same car that Toad stole earlier",
      "It is an undercover police car"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In The Wind in the Willows, Mr. Toad tries to hitchhike back to the River Bank community. What is the significance of the car and driver that give Toad a ride?",
    "questionId": "cd56e80a3fe99c9e14190f9411eb6aff",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "the weasels, stoats and ferrets",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "the weasels, stoats and ferrets",
      "the rabbits and otters",
      "the birds",
      "the squirrels and chipmunks"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "After his jail escape, The Wind in the Willows character, Toad, learns from Ratty that Toad Hall has been taken over by these Wild Wood animals.",
    "questionId": "c39ab78f00ac13d3dfb2a9c248513fa2",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The Legend of Sleepy Hollow",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Chicken Little",
      "Rip Van Winkle",
      "The Legend of Sleepy Hollow",
      "Mickey and the Beanstalk"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In 1949 Disney released their animated versions of The Wind in the Willows and this short story.",
    "questionId": "cdf64c52aa0ea771d0133f3225ce321c",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Pink Floyd",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "The Doors",
      "Jethro Tull",
      "The Beatles",
      "Pink Floyd"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In 1967 this British rock band released their first album. It was titled after Chapter 7 of The Wind in the Willows: The Piper at the Gates of Dawn.",
    "questionId": "cba62c7fddc790043bce7d52b0694ee6",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "a ride at Disneyland",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "a ride at Disneyland",
      "a brand of tennis shoes",
      "a Wyoming state police manual",
      "a board game"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Based on Mr. Toads car driving in The Wind in the Willows, Mr. Toads Wild Ride was established in 1955. What is it?",
    "questionId": "358590e26f7d23e60850dff8cd3ee4a8",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Mollusk Island",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Fairy Hollow",
      "London",
      "Never Land",
      "Mollusk Island"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Where does Peter live in the childrens novel Peter and the Shadow Thieves?",
    "questionId": "0a3f2c8879a44f16347fdd231e858416",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Shining Pearl",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Raven",
      "Dana",
      "Brilliant Ruby",
      "Shining Pearl"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In Peter and the Shadow Thieves, what is the name of Fighting Prawns oldest daughter?",
    "questionId": "2dda70ca784a2ef6943c409f1f1beab4",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "false",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Peter, the main character in Peter and the Shadow Thieves, wears shoes.",
    "questionId": "e1669d6090c0373aa42b96ab838d7105",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Teacher",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Singer",
      "Beauty",
      "Teacher",
      "Swimmer"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the name of the mermaid that flirts with Peter in the book Peter and the Shadow Thieves?",
    "questionId": "dca5dee7b0f2178a34f8e66a2a61e37d",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Molly",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Louise",
      "Tina",
      "Molly",
      "Julie"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Who does Peter have to warn about Ombra in the childrens novel Peter and the Shadow Thieves?",
    "questionId": "f6cf8e201596803571bf1317643d75eb",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the novel Peter and the Shadow Thieves, Slank is one of the Aster guards.",
    "questionId": "85dc4fa546cd0e221945fea265bcb4af",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "He goes by boat.",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "He takes a taxi.",
      "He goes by boat.",
      "He flies.",
      "He swims."
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "How does Peter get to London in the book Peter and the Shadow Thieves?",
    "questionId": "df60a653f9fab25938e8729107edbed5",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "White Tower",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Bloody Tower",
      "White Tower",
      "Prison Tower",
      "Golden Tower"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the book Peter and the Shadow Thieves, the starstuff was in what tower?",
    "questionId": "f5b7820c069b4f8d48ef0abbd90e5025",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the childrens novel Peter and the Shadow Thieves, James and Thomas are the two fastest Lost boys.",
    "questionId": "57c4806ee2d35a0aee5ee043045ace44",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Tinker Bell",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Rosy Tone",
      "Hornblower",
      "Tinker Bell",
      "Violet Vinger"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which fairy is Peters guardian in the book Peter and the Shadow Thieves?",
    "questionId": "5ecab1b650b65dbfae9546d8c41e58f7",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Brooks",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Brocks",
      "Books",
      "Brooks",
      "Brakes"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is Zoeys last name on the TV show Zoey 101?",
    "questionId": "bc1d9178021274e8a7a416c9382cf878",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "On the sitcom Zoey 101, Zoeys brothers name is Todd.",
    "questionId": "b1162d31c112b0a261ab805f4b410cb7",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "2005",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "2006",
      "2004",
      "2005",
      "2003"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What year did the TV series Zoey 101 hit the airwaves?",
    "questionId": "95c87dd4a50c8659df92d374e6803417",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Dean Rivers",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Mrs Rivers",
      "Dean Matthews",
      "Ms. Matthews",
      "Dean Rivers"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Who is the principal of the high school on Zoey 101?",
    "questionId": "e4a481e461799462cc9c0b90d9f2f703",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "PCA",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "ACP",
      "PAC",
      "PCA",
      "CAP"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the name of Zoeys high school on Zoey 101?",
    "questionId": "aa0c4c2e2afeef6021b525b8527cf5ce",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Quinn",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Quinn",
      "Nicole",
      "Ginger",
      "Gretchen"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the name of Zoeys brainiac friend on the sitcom Zoey 101?",
    "questionId": "9636bf9b0ecac5b0c7af97de94fdded5",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "She went to an all girls school.",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "She went to an all girls school.",
      "She got expelled.",
      "She moved away.",
      "She went to home school."
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What happened to Nicole on the TV show Zoey 101?",
    "questionId": "4d675aaed66bd81bd1a9c835a56ae31f",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Logan Ryan is the spoiled rich boy on Zoey 101.",
    "questionId": "5fe3f592be68f5743930c4d8a5019cc3",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "2008",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "2009",
      "2007",
      "2006",
      "2008"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "When did Zoey 101 end its original run?",
    "questionId": "b9480ce76cac6e61995d7be0c6040454",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Jamie Lynn Spears plays Zoey on Zoey 101.",
    "questionId": "277cc678f84b3dda107c2afbcb33a8b8",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "cow",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "cow",
      "panda",
      "bear",
      "monkey"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What type of animal is the school superintendent on Webkinz?",
    "questionId": "4d649939adfa1621391fd34fea087ce1",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "On Webkinz, there is a host for the Tournament Area.",
    "questionId": "cc04a9f11fa365f43e1aae3b9190452c",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "10",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "2",
      "5",
      "15",
      "10"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "How many tokens do you need to access the Wish Machine in Webkinz World?",
    "questionId": "d0b5eaf9f34224ac2ef0fcdc710ab264",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Dr. Quacks Clinic is the doctors office in Webkinz world.",
    "questionId": "193078262a70315cfe8afb116099d434",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "100",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "100",
      "10",
      "1",
      "50"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In Webkinz World, What is the maximum amount of Kinzcash (from the tips can) that Arte will accept?",
    "questionId": "51fb68594ce32466531040d69b2ae0c7",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Both",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Ginny",
      "Both",
      "Harry",
      "Said"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the 150th to last word in Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows?",
    "questionId": "43dd4a88da85f9da3299c5e35ddeaa2a",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "They",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "They",
      "Aberforth",
      "Came",
      "Hallows"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows, there is a chapter called The Bribe. What is the 138th word in this chapter?",
    "questionId": "d2de0aa61e3f19444b4b3a1997250fc0",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "By",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "It",
      "The",
      "By",
      "Hermione"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "This word is the 367th word of Hermiones Secret in Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban.",
    "questionId": "516fa27e9e92f91c15de4458609a4c43",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Send",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Sirius",
      "Grim",
      "Send",
      "Letter"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the 120th word in Grim Defeat, a chapter of Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban.",
    "questionId": "165e88a1240ef02e4fc3ad7d667a08a3",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Great",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Happy",
      "Hedwig",
      "Great",
      "Hagrid"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the 105th to last word in Diagon Alley, a chapter in Harry Potter and the Sorcerers/Philosophers Stone?",
    "questionId": "c40802a3db74f4c5e3d6fd1ea3b7759b",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Everyone",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Snake",
      "Filch",
      "Malfoy",
      "Everyone"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "This word is the 224th word of the chapter, titled The Midnight Duel in Harry Potter and the Sorcerers/Philosophers Stone.",
    "questionId": "043f2fcef4b7ce5a62a1eda47c94d08a",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Serpents",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Riddle",
      "Rocks",
      "Lockhart",
      "Serpents"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets has a chapter called The Chamber of Secrets. What is the 83rd to last word in this chapter?",
    "questionId": "5bd4269ca20b803bafcc38905a38ffcd",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Tongue",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Wand",
      "Malfoy",
      "Ron",
      "Tongue"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the Dueling Club, a chapter in Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets, what is the 251st to last word?",
    "questionId": "451f378bd98f05b33a6081f1873a13ae",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Throat",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Anyone",
      "Throat",
      "Elf",
      "Harry"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "This is word number 230 in the chapter Elf Tails in Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince.",
    "questionId": "f3c5b7d33a8d69d297c8d06e9d9684a6",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Wagging their tails behind them",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Wishing they never left",
      "Sooner then you think",
      "Waiting for their mommy",
      "Wagging their tails behind them"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Whats the last line of the nursery rhyme Little Bo Peep: Little Bo Peep has lost her sheep And cant tell where to find them. Leave them alone, And theyll come home, ..................................?",
    "questionId": "d5fbcd3502ad6387dae3d3d7205eda62",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "A diamond ring",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "A diamond ring",
      "A cart and bull",
      "A billy goat",
      "A looking glass"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Fill in the missing words in the nursery rhyme Hush, Little Baby: Hush, little baby, dont say a word Mamas gonna buy you a mockinbird If that mockinbird dont sing Mamas gonna buy you ....................",
    "questionId": "68f3564d2c7a751978047cc13ad488a3",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the following division problem, the quotient is 2: 12 / 6 = 2.",
    "questionId": "8a601288562e4b20e37a3061e3325fc2",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Taking a bath",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Scratching him/herself",
      "Trying to get attention",
      "Playing around",
      "Taking a bath"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "If your dog is licking him/herself, he/she is actually doing this.",
    "questionId": "dea074da5287763b63d934e4b05cbe79",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Use the bathroom in",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Play in",
      "Sleep in",
      "Use the bathroom in",
      "Eat in"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Kittens use the litter box as a place to what?",
    "questionId": "832a01771748f1c81c308074509a2bb8",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "false",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "When dogs lick you, to them it is the same as kissing you.",
    "questionId": "b6ad760ecd138c4d7d43039ef220e7d4",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "modifies nouns",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "modifies clauses",
      "modifies nouns",
      "modifies adjectives",
      "modifies verbs"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which of the following is NOT true about an adverb?",
    "questionId": "e1482d15109c8a7f2594bc261468ca7e",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "walking",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "her",
      "along",
      "walking",
      "Jane"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the participle in the following sentence?  Jane noticed her father walking along the shoreline.",
    "questionId": "4db061ad4d4628d403656cbf44127f01",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "lazy",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "door",
      "mom",
      "lazy",
      "car"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which of the following words can be used as an adjective?",
    "questionId": "8a933eee608e4cf2eb9f37601d1a7c8b",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Josh was driving down a one-way street.",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Josh could only go one-way.",
      "The cherries were chocolate-covered.",
      "Edgar Allen Poe is well-known.",
      "Josh was driving down a one-way street."
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Two words can be brought together as a compound word.  They can be written together (one way), written as one word (hairstylist) or written with a hyphen (forty-two).  Which of the following sentences is a correct usage of a hyphen?",
    "questionId": "9f7a2df2a2c45fbb21cf8500a597271d",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "noun",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "noun",
      "adjective",
      "adverb",
      "verb"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "The word effect is used as what part of speech in the following sentence?  Will lack of sleep have an effect on your performance at work?",
    "questionId": "1c24d37a3fc660adad65e83a382cb4eb",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Preparing and submitting his report to the review board for evaluation and possible publication, was one of the most difficult tasks Bill had ever attempted.",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "To stay in shape for competition, athletes must exercise on a regular basis to ensure top performance.",
      "Most of the evidence seemed convincing. Still, the credibility of some witnesses was in question.",
      "Preparing and submitting his report to the review board for evaluation and possible publication, was one of the most difficult tasks Bill had ever attempted.",
      "After the adjustment for inflation, real wages have decreased while corporate profits have grown."
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which of the following sentences uses a comma incorrectly?",
    "questionId": "0cd4bc4cef56a7e30a80cc36987eebae",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Harry Potter and the Sorcerers Stone",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets",
      "Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire",
      "Harry Potter and the Sorcerers Stone",
      "Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In which movie did Hermione Granger say the following: Im going to bed, before either one of you have another clever idea to get us killed, or worse, expelled",
    "questionId": "43eb615c3b3952ef0a9ec4845301b67e",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Sam",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Bam-Bam",
      "Jean-Claude Van Damme",
      "Sam",
      "A Lamb"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Complete this line from the classic childrens book Green Eggs and Ham: I am ______.",
    "questionId": "5db1ed93e7e1bea660d79f50bfab6646",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Fox",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Clock",
      "Dog with Chicken Pox",
      "Bag of Rocks",
      "Fox"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Complete this line from the book Green Eggs and Ham: I do not like them in a box! I do not like them with a _____!",
    "questionId": "bb40ea9a6fe222b095a445afd3ed1902",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Car",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Jeep",
      "Car",
      "Line at the DMV",
      "Bucket of boiled beets"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What word is missing in this line from the book Green Eggs and Ham: Would you? Could you? In a ........?",
    "questionId": "67e6c019e7996889ced96bdf3ade0833",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Beauty and the Beast",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "The Black Cauldron",
      "Sleeping Beauty",
      "Lady and the Tramp",
      "Beauty and the Beast"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In what Disney film does the following exchange take place: I want to do something for her... but what? Well, theres the usual things: flowers... chocolates... promises you dont intend to keep... ?",
    "questionId": "8d04d48b33ce542e96fc618c3e9b2fd9",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The Emperors New Groove",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "The Emperors New Groove",
      "The Brave Little Toaster",
      "Mulan",
      "A Goofy Movie"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What Disney film is this dialogue from: Uh-oh. Dont tell me. Were about to go over a huge waterfall. Yep. Sharp rocks at the bottom? Most likely. Bring it on?",
    "questionId": "25bd97e715b8f64820beb186e8bbcb71",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "2",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "4",
      "2",
      "8",
      "6"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What does x equal in this equation? 4x+4=12",
    "questionId": "1e07821b962439d21e93a9141f45dae0",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "5",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "0",
      "5",
      "10",
      "2"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the answer to the following: (2*5)-5",
    "questionId": "6546832b5e34eb3bf5e5b0de45f610c0",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "true",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Is this correct? 2-3+1-4+4-=0",
    "questionId": "313a70a19de688841b1905ba84c7d72f",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "16",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "16",
      "17",
      "14",
      "15"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is the missing number? 2,4,7,11,?,22",
    "questionId": "7dc9176aa7f5f8f5a272110ca4ce63df",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "2002",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "2001",
      "2000",
      "2002",
      "2003"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What year did the animated series The Adventures of Jimmy Neutron: Boy Genius 1st air?",
    "questionId": "01b18d76f63265765980a4d430240bc2",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Carl and Sheen",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Carl and Bolbi",
      "Carl and Sheen",
      "Bolbi and Nick",
      "Sheen and Bob"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Who  are Jimmys best friends on the show The Adventures of Jimmy Neutron: Boy Genius?",
    "questionId": "9eb13ce0ef71e43987fef8d8ecd0b065",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Folfax and Vortex",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Johnson and Vortex",
      "Folfax and Vortex",
      "Weed and Anderson",
      "Williams and Washington"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What are Libbys and Cindys last names on the animated show The Adventures of Jimmy Neutron: Boy Genius?",
    "questionId": "10466ebae17d465d1bfebed659e4d146",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The N-Men",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Super  Justice League",
      "The Tomorrow Boys",
      "The N-Men",
      "Fundemonium"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In what episode of The Adventures of Jimmy Neutron: Boy Genius are Jimmy and friends diagnosed with superpowers?",
    "questionId": "bf324ccaf815b52bc0f8dd3d60241f6e",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "UltraLord",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Bat Man",
      "UltraLord",
      "Speed Boy",
      "Super Man"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "On the animated show The Adventures of Jimmy Neutron: Boy Genius, who is Sheens favorite  superhero?",
    "questionId": "d4add2610d32a776c848888f82a59cd9",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Retroville",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Oak Town",
      "Retro Park",
      "Retroland",
      "Retroville"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What city do Jimmy and his friends live in on the show The Adventures of Jimmy Neutron: Boy Genius?",
    "questionId": "cbe854bb999c74f18879cfce33805090",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "True",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the series The Adventures of Jimmy Neutron: Boy Genius, Jimmy has a crush on Cindy.",
    "questionId": "23e4d3e7077334b9a0842b5213dc4467",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Hugh",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Robert",
      "James",
      "Joseph",
      "Hugh"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is Jimmys dads name on The Adventures of Jimmy Neutron: Boy Genius?",
    "questionId": "3dae0461589e41508a978ae387e7bd69",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "pie",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "pie",
      "cookies",
      "pizza",
      "cake"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "What is Jimmys dads favorite food on The Adventures of Jimmy Neutron: Boy Genius?",
    "questionId": "3d3ca4941b3cbaacccfb4c52ddce12cb",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Ms. Fowl",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Ms. Fowl",
      "Mrs. Poultry",
      "Ms. Turkey",
      "Ms. Chicken"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Who is the teacher of fictional character Jimmy Neutron?",
    "questionId": "f8efc5a709fda3370074b406edb3dcf9",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "true",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Animated character Jimmy Neutron has a brother.",
    "questionId": "7d4a4e9614d36e70544d24fee14ecca3",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Fear of monsters under your bed",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Fear of monsters under your bed",
      "Fear of lemon meringue pie",
      "Fear of heights",
      "Fear of realtors"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which of these is a rational fear according to the book the The Wide Window by Lemony Snicket?",
    "questionId": "6ed288c48745ccaff061b5946f81012c",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In the book The Austere Academy, when Carmelita Spats called the Baudelaires cakesniffers, Mr. Poe said that was very rude of her.",
    "questionId": "9aa181351736d275a4383a0efbe25456",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The Vile Village",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "The Penultimate Peril",
      "The Wide Window",
      "The Vile Village",
      "The Bad Beginning"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In which book by Lemony Snicket does the phrase, It takes a village to raise a child, affect the Baudelaires?",
    "questionId": "97d5f0d51cf31ceeedd090f2ac2ae213",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "They are just rectangles of black.",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "They are just rectangles of black.",
      "They look like someone spilled tea on them.",
      "They can only be read if you hold the book up to a mirror.",
      "They are deliberately placed out of order."
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which statement is true about some of the pages of the book The Ersatz Elevator?",
    "questionId": "816683a382858971356ac1651d8aa072",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "The Carnivorous Carnival",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "The Carnivorous Carnival",
      "The Reptile Room",
      "The Grim Grotto",
      "The Vile Village"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In which book of A Series of Unfortunate Events are there two pages that are almost identical?",
    "questionId": "c21a3dcdd068f337f7d697c245bce0cc",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "To Beatrice, I always used to sleep late on weekends. Alas, now you do, also.",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "To Beatrice, when I first saw you, I was breathless. Now, you are.",
      "To Beatrice, summer without you is as cold as winter. Winter without you is even colder.",
      "To Beatrice, I always used to sleep late on weekends. Alas, now you do, also.",
      "To Beatrice, you will always be in my mind, in my heart, and in your grave."
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Every book of A Series of Unfortunate Events is dedicated to Beatrice, followed by a short message. Which of the following sentences was never written on the dedication page?",
    "questionId": "b6527ccdc3d6a520d29dd0002776b91c",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Nectarine",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Ratennice",
      "Centarine",
      "Nectarine",
      "Nernatice"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Decode the name of this fruit: tenceniar",
    "questionId": "2e4dc5f1fde089197b167cd365eb35d8",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Beatrice Baudelaire",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "A metaphor for V. F. D.",
      "Beatrice Quagmire",
      "Beatrice Baudelaire",
      "Aunt Josephines sister"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Who is the Beatrice that writer Lemony Snicket always dedicates his books to?",
    "questionId": "b85617de19a1a218962e55312746ce5e",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Sailing on a boat",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Settling on an island",
      "Crying",
      "Sailing on a boat",
      "Dying"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "The 13th book of A Series of Unfortunate Events ends with the Baudelaires doing what?",
    "questionId": "5f0b668ba5eb33ecd67cdc0a73960a4b",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "The final 13th book of A Series of Unfortunate Events has 13 chapters and ends with an About the author... section.",
    "questionId": "fef9a7d8935e130e005a5c6e508bbeb5",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Klaus Baudelaire, Sunny Baudelaire, Duncan Quagmire",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Count Olaf, Mr. Baudelaire, Carmelita Spats",
      "Violet Baudelaire, Jerome Squalor, Aunt Josephine",
      "Violet Baudelaire, Klaus Baudelaire, Beatrice Snicket",
      "Klaus Baudelaire, Sunny Baudelaire, Duncan Quagmire"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which set of characters from A Series of Unfortunate Events contains only people who lived through the entire series?",
    "questionId": "f95b0227b1196b8e9335ff9274853756",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "False",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Esme Squalors evilness was due to her boyfriend, Count Olaf.",
    "questionId": "6da74896338bf0510f5d647b600cc781",
    "questionType": "true-false"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Card game",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Ball game",
      "Card game",
      "Board game",
      "Word game"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In A Series of Unfortunate Events, what type of game did Fionas brother invent?",
    "questionId": "d7e46c521ef88cc351aa95dfda263710",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Jaques Snicket, Jerome Squalor, Justice Strauss",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Jaques Snicket, Joseph Spat, Judy Spree",
      "Jaques Snicket, Judy Spree, Justice Strauss",
      "Jaques Snicket, Jerome Squalor, Justice Strauss",
      "Joseph Spat, Jerome Squalor, Justice Strauss"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "Which three names can J.S. stand for in the books of A Series of Unfortunate Events?",
    "questionId": "75d4ddd7f8efa001bdc02986b6281814",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  },
  {
    "answer": "Book 4",
    "category": "for-kids",
    "choices": [
      "Book 4",
      "Book 5",
      "Book 2",
      "Book 3"
    ],
    "newCategory": "For Kids",
    "question": "In which book of A Series of Unfortunate Events did Klauss glasses break?",
    "questionId": "5617739726ea8ee0e10fff06c0a71ce4",
    "questionType": "multiple-choice"
  }
]